我刚刚做了个奇怪的梦
I just had the strangest dream.
是在星期五
It's Friday.
我们在医院
We're at the hospital.
但也不是医院 应该算是森林
But it's not a hospital, it's a forest of sorts.
因为在你的身旁有一头熊
And I know that because right next to you there's a bear.
一头灰熊 把脚伸到小溪里冲凉
A grizzly, cooling his feet in a stream.
突然之间 你就开始分娩...
And all of a sudden, you begin to deliver...
而我不在你身边
...and I can't get to you.
但是熊在你的身边
But the bear can.
过了一会儿...
And next thing I know...
他就抱着我们漂亮的儿子
...he is holding our beautiful baby boy.
接下来的是就怪了! 噢 ....
And here's where it gets odd. Uh....
它咬断了脐带
He chews the cord.
但奇怪的是 我对此并不介意
But, strangely, I'm okay with it.
这一定是个好兆头
That's gotta be a good sign.
希奥多 这名字好是好
Theodore. Loved it.
记得那篇给孩子取名的文章吗?
But remember that article I told you about? Naming kids after famous people?
这会让泰德将来背上 很大的成功压力
I don't want Teddy to think he's a failure if he doesn't wind up on Mount Rushmore.
噢 亚瑟 噢!
Uh, Arthur. Oh!
这不好念 这个名字有神话 古典的感觉
This was tough, because it's mythological. Round Table, the whole deal.
不过你记得" 名字游戏 "吗?
But "The Name Game." Remember that?
"名字游戏" ?
"The Name Game"?
"亚瑟 Art- bo- Bart 香蕉 Fana- fo- Fart "
"Art- Art- bo- Bart, Banana- Fana- fo- Fart."
然后还有凯西
Brings us to Casey.
以及很多名字
This whole next slew of names:
凯西 乔丹 狄伦 德鲁 泰勒 应该还有史盖勒...
Casey, Jordan, Dylan, Drew, Taylor, Tyler and probably mostly Skylar...
全部都像是女孩的名字
...are all names that could be girls' names.
我们为什么不干脆点 直接给他取个女孩的名字呢?
Why don't we just cut to the chase and call him Cindy?
是啊 我真想离开亚特兰大这个地方
Yeah, Atlanta. Trying to get out of this place.
- 能去丹佛就好了 - 嗯
- Denver's where it's at, man. - Mm- hm.
那里有很多政府丑闻
They got the whole underground government conspiracy thing going on.
- 是吗? - 我在网路上....
- That so? - I'm hearing a lot of chatter...
- 看到很多传言 - 对不起 接个电话
- ...on the message boards. - Gotcha. I should grab this.
- 抱歉 喂 宝贝 - 嗨! 老公
- Sorry. Hey, honey. Hey, sweetie.
- 你有收到我的留言了吗? - 收到了
- Did you get my message? - I did.
我听到一半 就累到不行了
I'm about halfway through it. I thought I'd take a little break.
哈 我并不是说这些名字不行
Ha, ha. I didn't want you to think I was arbitrarily dismissing those names.
你也考虑的很仔细
You considered them carefully.
不过这是个大事 知道吗?
It's just such a big decision, you know?
我知道 你把这当成天大的事
I know. Clearly, you're taking it very seriously.
更重要的是 你现在穿着什么?
More importantly, what are you wearing?
阿曼尼 西装
Armani Exchange.
我是问我的...不 不 我在和司机说话 宝贝
I'm talking to my... No, no, that's just the driver, baby.
好了 我要下车了 我挂了
Okay, listen, I'm about to be dropped off. I should go.
- 我爱你 很想早点见到你 - 我也爱你 一路顺风
- I love you, can't wait to see you. - I love you too. Safe flying.
- 到了 - 好的
- Here you go. - Perfect.
好
Yep.
搞什么啊?
What in the eff?
- 该死的! - 一下撞了上来
- Goddamn it! - We done knocked it right off.
喂 老兄! 你刚刚撞了我的车!
Hey, man! You just hit my car!
- 你刚把我的车门撞掉 老兄 - 很抱歉
- You just knocked my door off, man. Sorry about that.
还好没伤到人吧?
First things first, is everybody okay?
我这是辆豪华轿车! 你不知道机场行车的规矩吗?
I'm in a Town Car! Don't you know airport protocol?
豪华轿车总是有优先权!
Town Cars have the right of way always!
这里有一些严重破损
That right there is some serious damage.
这可不是小事!
That ain't shit!
我姐夫肯定发飙 没完没了!
My brother- in- law is gonna kill me. I'm through!
没伤到你吧?
You okay?
都是我朋友不好 他喝了点酒
Sorry about my friend. He's been drinking.
你也一身酒味 你们边喝酒边开车吗?
You smell boozy too. Drinking and driving together?
嗯 我们没一直喝酒
Well, we haven't been drinking.
我的意思是 只喝了6罐啤酒 但是 ....
I mean, we split a six- pack. Of 40s. But....
你知道吗?
You know what?
我的父亲常说
My father always had a saying:
一大早就倒楣时 这天都会有好运
When a day starts like this, it's all uphill from here.
这话实际上是错的
That's actually incorrect.
- 我爸爸常这么说 - 不 应该是这一天都会有霉运
- My dad used to say it. - No, it's all downhill from here.
人人都希望有好运 没人希望有霉运
Everybody wants to be up. Nobody wants to be down.
但是霉运的可能性更大 你爸根本就是胡说八道
It's easier as you go down. He didn't know what he was talking about.
- 喂 谢尔比? 怎么样 - 我们没事 老兄 我能处理
- Hey, Shelby? We good? - We're cool, man. I'll take care of it.
- 好 - 你去吧 大明星!
- Okay. Go get them, Hollywood!
喂! 先生 你把我的行李撞倒了
Excuse me. Sir? You mind picking these up?
在机场我不能接触 其他人的行李
I can't. You're not supposed to touch other people's luggage at an airport.
你自己的行李 自己处理吧
Handle your own baggage.
检查行李!
Bag check!
- 先生 这你的包吗? - 对 有什么问题?
- This your bag, sir? - Is there a problem?
- 我要搜查一下 先生 - 好的 请便
- I'm gonna have to search it real quick, sir. - Yeah. Feel free.
幽默杂志吗? 你可真行啊
Mad magazine? That's cute.
那不是我的
That's not mine.
- 这是你的包吗? - 那不是 ...
- This is your bag? - That's not...
好东西喔!
Jackpot!
那绝对不是我的 我一定被那家伙掉包了
That's definitely not mine. My bag got switched with this...
- 是你亲自装的行李吗? - 但不是这个包啦
- You packed your bag yourself? - But not that.
我从未吸过毒 这真是荒唐
I've never done drugs in my life. This is absolutely... This is crazy.
说不定是贩毒的
Maybe you a drug mule.
- 怎么 我看起来像是贩毒的? - 难说喔 毒贩子长怎样
- Do I look like a drug mule? - I don't know, how do drug mules look?
- 你比我清楚 - 像我这模样吗?
- You're the expert. - What, like me?
- 我可没说 - 但你的眼神里有这意思
- Who said that? - Your eyes.
眼神? 我可没说 我不觉得你模样看起来像....
My eyes said something? Did my mouth? I don't think you look like a...
你不要这么乱翻好不好
Do you mind not tossing it up so much?
呜! 你这小子可真时髦啊
Whoo! Funky motherfucker, ain't you?
你这样回应非常不得体
You are so inappropriate, it's crazy.
别人对我有很多评价 不过说我 "不得体"
I been called a lot of things, but "inappropriate"?
那还是破天荒 头一回哩
That's some fucked- up shit, yo.
噢 我的天啊
Oh, my goodness.
看这 宝贝
Look at this, Sonny.
多豪华
Fancy.
就像在天堂里
Died and gone to heaven.
难到你看不见 这里坐着一个人吗?
Are you not aware that there's a person here?
抱歉
Sorry.
噢 是你啊!
Well, hello!
你好啊?
How you doing?
怎么来头等舱了?
What brings you up to first class?
我的位子....
The seat that I procured...
- 噢 抱歉 - 借过
Oh, sorry. Excuse me.
我本来在三等舱 但是我的安全带 坏了 就把我安排到头等舱了
I was in low class, and my seat belt didn't work, and they bumped me up.
这是经济舱
It's called economy.
今天日子真幸运 很高兴见到你
Lucky day. Nice to see you.
很抱歉 刚认识的时候有些不愉快....
Sorry how we met, but, you know....
噢 对了
Oh, you know what?
- 我们好像拿错了行李 - 我知道
- I think we switched our bags at the curb. - I know we did.
你的包被没收 里面有私人物品
Your bag was confiscated. It had paraphernalia in it.
大烟枪
Marijuana pipe.
嗯 那是一种医疗仪器
Well, that's a medical apparatus.
- 我患有青光眼 - 得了吧 你有青光眼
- I have glaucoma. - Sure, you have glaucoma.
各位乘客请注意 在起飞以前 请关闭所有电子仪器 ...
Attention, in preparation for takeoff, please turn off all electronic devices...
如果有笔记型电脑 请收起来 感谢合作 祝你旅途愉快
...and if you have a laptop, please stow it. Thank you and enjoy your flight.
刚广播了 你应该关掉
They made the announcement. You should turn that off.
- 是的 我听到了 - 你就关掉吧 知道为什么吗?
- Yeah, I get it. - Just turn it off. You know why?
- 这就关掉 - 这是因为他们不安 ...
- I'm gonna turn it off. - They get uneasy...
因为他们知道恐怖分子经常用 手机引爆行李里的炸弹
...because they know terrorists use their phones to trigger bombs in their luggage.
嘘 嘘 嘘~
Shh. Pst, pst, pst.
- 这句话不能胡乱说 - 哪句话"恐怖分子"还是"炸弹" ?
- That's not the word you want to say. - "Terrorist" or "bomb"?
- 你两句话都说了 - 这我知道
- You said both the words. - I understand.
- 我只是想告诉你... - 不用你说 听我说
- I'm trying to tell you that I read... - Stop trying to tell me and listen.
你不该说引起别人恐慌的话
Don't say words that put people on edge.
- 我只是想让你知道 - 这很不礼貌
- I'm trying to be informative. - It's not cool.
先生 对不起 你能和你的朋友 来一下吗?
Would you and your friend mind stepping to the front of the plane?
我的朋友?
My friend?
先生 我需要你 跟我一起来
I'm sorry, I need you to come with me, please.
听着 我从未见过这个小丑
Listen. This clown, I've never seen before in my life.
不是的 我们在路边调换过行李
That's not true. We switched bags at curbside.
- 那是不小心的 而他... - 先生!
- That was an accident. And he had... Sir!
我是联邦空警 请到飞机前面来
Federal air marshal. Please step to the front of the plane.
什么? 为什么?
What? Why?
放下装置
Drop the device.
- 这不是什么装置 它是手机 - 放下装置! 浑蛋
- It's not a device, it's a BlackBerry. - Drop the device!
你还能对我开枪不成 冒牌警察?
What are you gonna do, rent- a- cop? Shoot me...?
大家不要惊慌 他不要紧
It's okay, everyone. He'll be fine.
这是橡胶子弹
It's only a rubber bullet.
好消息 海曼先生 在飞机找到你的行李
Good news, Mr. Highman. They found your bags on the airplane.
- 噢 好啊 - 遗憾的是 飞机已在堪萨斯州上空
- Oh, good. - Unfortunately, that plane's over Kansas.
- 不出所料 - 不过你的手机在这里
- Figures. - But I do have your cell phone for you.
现在 请你在这文件上签字 就是释放文件
Now, if you wouldn't mind just signing this. It's a simple release.
避免我被起诉?
So I don't sue you.
对 写的是我们都次依法行事
Just saying we acted in accordance with state law.
- 当然 - 好的
- Sure did. - Good.
在这里写下你的地址 我们好把你的行李寄回去
If you put your address there, I'll have your bags shipped.
不用了 就留在洛杉矶机场吧 我去取 下一班航机是什么时候?
Let them land at LAX and I'll pick them up when I get there. When's the next flight?
- 一小时后 但你坐不上 - 为什么呢?
- ln an hour, but you won't be on it. - Why's that?
你被列入禁飞名单了
You're on the No- Fly list.
- 为什么? - 上面就这么写着
- Why? - It says right here.
- 你还有你的朋友 - 谁?
- You and your friend. - Who?
- 我刚刚和他谈过 - 我从未见过那个浑蛋
- The gentleman I just interviewed. - I've never seen that dipshit before.
- 真的吗? - 是的
- Really? - Yeah.
- 他可说了你不少好话 - 我在禁飞名单里? 真是可笑
- He had nice things to say about you. - I'm on a No- Fly list? This is ridiculous.
- 不加理会 ... - 不
- Regardless... - No.
我妻子怀孕了 我必须回洛杉矶 这肯定是搞错了
I have a pregnant wife, I have to get back. This is a huge misunderstanding.
- 我能怎么办 - 你看过 阿甘正传吗?
- What am I supposed to do? - Have you ever seen Forrest Gump?
看过
Yes.
嗯 他是走过去的 他是笨蛋
Well, he ran across country, and he was pretty stupid.
因此我相信你比他强
So I have faith in you.
你可以离开了
You're free to leave.
出了什么事?
What kind of incident?
我..也没什么啦
I'm probably overstating.
小事一桩 我能处理
It's the manageable kind. A micro- incident.
但遗憾的是 我被列入禁飞名单了
But it unfortunately landed me on a No- Fly list.
你做什么? 你对别人发脾气了吗?
What did you do, Peter? Did you snap at somebody?
不! 我没有 我自始至终都 很平静 克制情绪
Nope. I did not. I was cool, calm and collected the whole time.
完全没做任何出格的事
I was completely in my rights.
你有时也容易冲动
You get so carried away sometimes.
那你怎样回家?
How are you gonna get home?
我有个计画 而这个计画正在实现
I have a plan. And the plan is sorting itself out.
- 不过我的钱包在飞机上 - 什么?
- But my wallet is traveling. - What?
身分证也在里面 我想租辆汽车 我记得办公室传真....
The ID's in it, I've been trying to rent a car, I had the office fax...
不过我正想尽办法去
But I am exhausting any and all opportunities to...
嘿! 我一直在找你
Hey! I've been looking all over for you.
- 离我远一点 你净惹麻烦 - 但是我捡到你的一样东西
- Stay away from me. But I found something of yours.
宝贝 事情应该解决了 我先挂了
Honey, this might all be solved. I'll call you right back.
彼得?
Peter?
你有我的东西?
You got my stuff?
- 在逮捕我之前 我拿到的 - 猴子?
- I grabbed it before they zip- tied me. - Rally Monkey?
- 我的钱包在你那里吗? - 我没看见
- You get my wallet? - I didn't see it.
那我的行李呢?
Where's my bag?
我看到你的行李 但是我拿不了
I saw your bag, but I didn't grab it because my hands were full.
因为我的手上还拿着它
You know, I had this thing in my hand.
- 你租了哪辆汽车? - 没有 因为我没有驾照...
- What kind of car did you get? - I didn't, because I don't have a license...
在我的钱包里 而钱包正在...对吧!
...because it's in my wallet that's on the.... Right?
靠夭哩 你还真是不走运 !!
Oh, shoot. What a bummer.
是啊 不走运 !!
Yeah, bummer.
谢谢你把玩偶带来了
Thanks for the doll.
真它妈的白痴
Fucking idiot.
喂 你想和我一起走吗?
Hey, you wanna ride with us?
不用了 我其实不是很喜欢狗
No, I'm fine. I'm not really a big dog person.
好吧 我知道我们 开始相处并不愉快
Look, I know we got off on the wrong foot.
不过了解我之后 你会发现我这人还挺不错的
But I have a really great personality once you get to know me.
是啦 你能多好啊
Yeah, I'm sure you do.
我在脸书上有90个好友 有12个没加我 但毕竟有90位好友
I got 90 friends on Facebook. Twelve pending, but I got 90 friends.
费用我来承担
I'll cover expenses.
当我们到了好莱坞时 你在还我也不迟
You can pay me back when we get to Hollywood.
- 洛杉矶 - 啊?
- L.A. - Huh?
那城市部叫好莱坞 叫洛杉矶
It's not called Hollywood. It's Los Angeles.
但是我要去好莱坞
Yeah, but I'm going to Hollywood.
你叫什么名字?
What's your name?
彼得
Peter.
我的名字是伊森 伊森·崔布雷
My name's Ethan. Ethan Tremblay.
而这个小家伙...
And this little guy...
这小胖子...
...this little butterball...
它叫桑尼
...this is Sonny.
和你一起走势我们的荣幸 来吧
And we would be honored to have you ride with us. Come on.
会很有意思的
It'll be fun.
开个玩笑 哈哈
JK. LOL.
上车吧
"Hop in."
世事难料啊 不是吗? 系上安全带
Life's weird, isn't it? Buckle up.
- 你有兄弟或者姐妹吗? - 没有
- You have any brothers or sisters? - No.
- 你有养狗吗? - 没有
- You have a dog? - Nope.
那好吧问你个问题 你最喜爱的颜色是什么?
Let me ask you this: What's your favorite color?
- 蓝色 - 好酷喔 我喜欢绿色
- Blue. - That's so cool. Mine's green.
哇啊
Wow.
- 你喜欢热狗吗? - 是的
- Do you like hot dogs? - Yes, I do.
我更喜欢玉米热狗
I'm more of a corn- dog man, myself.
我曾经在裸体的海滩上吃过 一根老二形状得热狗
I once ate a foot- long corn dog on a nude beach.
就吃过那一回
I'll never do that again.
- 你几岁不是处男? - 我不想谈论这个话题
- At what age did you lose your virginity? - I'm not gonna discuss that.
- 我是在 9 岁 - 小孩?
- I was 9 years old. - Boy.
她是个好女孩 好女孩
Great gal. Great gal.
叫 "青春痘" 希拉
Sheila Pimples.
我有点头痛 不是因为你
I'm getting a headache, not because of you.
我是因为心事太多
It's just, I'm under a lot of pressure.
我老婆快要生了
My wife and I are having a baby.
- 星期五是预产期 所以我买了猴子 - 噢 真的吗?
- On Friday. That's who the monkey's for. - Oh, really?
- 真的 是剖腹产 - 真好
- Yep. C- section. - That's sweet.
- 所以希望你能....感谢 - 我理解 完全理解
- So if we could just.... Thanks. - I understand. God, I totally understand.
我要去好莱坞见一位大经纪人
I was supposed to meet a bigtime agent in Hollywood.
幸运的是 他延后面会时间了
Luckily, he postponed.
- 这么说你是演员 - 对
- So you're an actor. - Yep.
干脆这样吧
Yep. You know what?
你帮我看看这几张造型如何啊
In fact, I wouldn't mind having a fresh pair of eyes...
喂 喂 喂
Hey, hey, hey.
对不起! 你帮我看看
My apologies. Look at this.
- 好 你看着路 - 没问题
- Okay. If you'd just look at the road. - I got it.
- 噢 你的半身照 - 半身照
- Oh, your headshots. - Headshots.
这张看上去像是悠闲的人...
This one, this is a laid- back guy with a Hawaiian shirt...
不过他带着一枝枪
...but he packs a piece.
- 有意思 - 是啊
- lnteresting. - Yep.
这张是我父亲最喜欢的
This one was my father's favorite.
他说这张最能表现我的性格
He says it really showed my spirit.
而我也这么认为
And I agree with him.
这是什么...
What's that, a...?
分别是扮演黑社会 建筑工 和....
That's a gang member, a construction worker, and....
一个书呆子 教授
And a nerd. A professor.
不 我是扮演马尔科姆
No. I'm Malcolm X.
它还真把自己当人 笨狗
He thinks he's human. So stupid.
你来亚特兰大是生意还是旅游?
What brought you to Atlanta? Business or pleasure?
- 生意 - 生意
- Business. - Business.
哪种生意?
What kind of business?
建筑
Architecture.
- 你怎么进入建筑行业的? - 学这专业 还有其他问题吗?
- How'd you get into architecture? - College. Anything else?
- 如果没有 我就吃饭了 - 对不起
- Because I'm trying to... - I'm sorry.
我们毕竟要相处几天 认识一下彼此也是好的嘛
We're gonna be traveling. It wouldn't hurt to get to know each other.
好吧
Okay.
伊森 你来亚特兰大 是生意还是旅游?
Ethan, what brought you to Atlanta? Business or pleasure?
我爸去世了
My daddy died.
我去亚特兰大是参加葬礼
I went to Atlanta to go to his funeral.
喔 对不起 我不知道 抱歉
Gee, I didn't know. I'm sorry.
他是个好人 老兄 是它让我去西部的原因
He was a great guy, man. That's why I'm heading out West.
是他激励我进入影视业的
He's the one that motivated me to get on the TV.
- 影视业吗? - 是的
- TV? - Yeah.
要进入这一行不容易啊
Tough business to break into.
竞争很激烈
So competitive.
我有位朋友 就干这一行
I have a friend, he's in that industry.
- 他演过 好汉两个半吗? - 没有 他....
- Does he work on Two and a HalfMen? - No. He...
那太遗憾了 就是看了好汉两个半
That's too bad. Because Two and a Half Men...
所以我才想要做一名演员
...is the reason I wanted to become an actor.
- 是吗 - 特别是第 2 季
- Right. - Especially the second season.
我们计画这么走
Here's the plan.
我们刚离开 伯明翰...
We are just outside Birmingham...
我们动身有点晚 因此今天 只能刚进到路易士安那州
...and we got a late start, so we will only make it just to inside Louisiana.
明天早点赶路
Early to bed, early to rise.
需要16至18个小时长途行驶 才能够到达亚利桑那州 菲尼克斯
Long 1 6- to 1 8- hour haul, which will land us in Phoenix, Arizona.
- 这样离洛杉矶就剩8小时车程了 - 你知道更好的是
- Eight hours outside of L.A. - You know what'd be nice?
如果我们能在大峡谷停留一下
If we could stop at the Grand Canyon.
我们不去大峡谷 原因是
We're not going to the Grand Canyon.
这比我们的最佳路线 多出120英里
That would be easily 1 20 miles off our optimum route.
那太遗憾了
That's too bad.
因为我爸爸很喜欢大峡谷
Daddy would've loved the Grand Canyon.
你怎么还留着它?
Why do you even have this?
噢 因为这就是我爸
Oh, because this is my daddy.
里面是他的骨灰
These are his ashes.
为什么你把父亲的骨灰 装在咖啡罐里?
Why are your father's ashes in a coffee can, Ethan?
因为他死啊 彼得
Because he's dead, Peter.
- 这点我知道啦 - 我的话你都没听见吗?
- I know. I know that part. - Don't you listen to anything?
我只是说 一般都放在骨灰坛里
I'm just saying, normal people put remains in an urn.
这是真空密封的
This is vacuum- sealed.
当你倒出咖啡时 就打开密封盖了
You broke the seal when you poured out the coffee.
装上你父亲的骨灰再盖上盖子 那不叫真空密封
You poured your father's remains in and closed it. That didn't reseal it.
我从没听过这么愚蠢的话
That's the dumbest thing I've ever heard in my life.
天啊 我们不该来这里的
God. We shouldn't have come here.
我对蛋奶烘饼过敏
I'm allergic to waffles.
跟我来 桑尼 谢谢
Come on, Sonny. Thank you.
我们要在伯明翰 简短停留一下
We need to make a brief pit stop in Birmingham.
实际上 我们的下一站是什里夫波特 在那里休息
Actually, our next stop is Shreveport. That's where we rest.
- 只要 10分钟车程 - 就算我们能到
- It's 1 0 minutes away. - Let's see if we can make it.
为何要去伯明翰呢? 我们要赶时间
Why you making a pit stop in Birmingham? We gotta make time.
因为我治疗青光眼的药在飞机上
I left my glaucoma medication on the plane.
等等 你说什么?
Wait, wait, wait. Your what?
你是说你的大麻?
You mean your weed?
- 那是药用大麻 彼得! - 不 它就是大麻
- It's medical marijuana, Peter. - No, it's weed.
- 你为什么老往坏处想? - 它就是大麻
- Why do you make everything so dark? - It's weed.
我只是不想为了毒品 耽误时间 可以吗?
I'm saying I really don't want to stop and buy drugs. Is that okay?
有些话我不想要说 是你逼我的
I didn't want to play this card, certainly not this early.
你以为这车是谁的 是我的
But guess what. Guess who's got the Subaru lmpreza. Me.
你猜谁身上有钱? 也是我
Guess who's got all the money. Me.
你再猜谁脾气比较好 更是我
Guess who's got a winning personality. Me.
你到底有什么? 也就是只有发型好看点
What do you have? You have a nice hairline, fine.
下巴方正些
You have a strong jaw, fine.
不过我告诉你 老兄
But I gotta tell you something, mister.
你的脾气 真得改改
Your personality needs some work.
真是的..
My God.
现在 你到底想不想回洛杉矶?
Now, do you want a ride to California or not?
- 想 ! 麻烦您 - 那就好 拿着我爸爸
- Yes, please. - Good. Hold Dad.
- 爸爸! - 对不起 我拿着了 拿着了
- Dad! - I'm sorry. I got it. I got it, I got it.
我的天啊 你怎么跟个孩子似的
Okay. God Almighty, holy moly. It's like I'm traveling with a child.
- 你去过厕所了吗? - 好建议 我去小便
- Did you use the restroom? - I need to take a pee- pee.
- 彼得吗? - 问题解决了 我在车上了
- Peter? - Crisis averted, I'm driving.
- 怎么有车的? - 让我和她说两句
- Driving how? - Let me talk to her.
和一个刚在....请不要这样! 在租车公司认识的人一起
With a guy... Please don't. With a guy that I met in a rent- a- car.
这么远的路程 和一个刚认识的一起走?
You're gonna drive 2000 miles with a guy you just met?
他是....
Say hi to...
莎拉吗? 嗨 我是伊森·崔布雷 正与彼得一起开车 你好吗?
Sarah? Hi, this is Ethan Tremblay. I'm riding with Peter. How are you?
我很好啊 你好吗?
I'm fine. How are you?
很好 想要让你知道 你的行李以带上了 完好无损
Good, good. I wanted to let you know I have your package, and he is A- okay.
我会在星期四以前送达
And I will have him delivered by Thursday.
非常感谢
Thank you so much.
嘿 莎拉 还有件事请教 你认识些什么理发师吗?
Hey, Sarah? One other thing. Do you have a hairdresser out West?
我漂亮的头发需要修剪一下
I got this killer perm, and it needs major upkeep.
对不起 你说你烫发了?
I'm sorry, did you say that you have a perm?
是的 烫发 是一种发型
Yeah, a perm. Like a permanent.
- 难看死了 - 你介意吗?
- It's heinous. - Do you mind?
- 我能和我丈夫谈谈吗? - 好的 稍等一下
- Can I just talk to my husband, please? - Yeah. Okay, hold on.
- 她要和你谈谈 - 我知道
- She wants to talk to you. - I know.
- 我就是和他打交道 - 噢 我的天啊
- So that's what I'm dealing with. - Oh, my God.
对啊 祈求上帝保佑我们吧
Yep. God bless us all.
- 别担心 - 我没有啦
- Stop worrying. - I'm not worried.
她是合法生意 我在网路上认识的
She's very legitimate. I found her on Craigslist.
哪一位?
Who is it?
好极了...
Fantastic.
嗨妳好 我是伊森 刚才打过电话给你
Hi. It's Ethan. I called you earlier.
说实在的 你尽快买完就走吧
Honestly, like two minutes, okay? Just buy it and then go.
- 嗨 - 嗨
- Hey. - Hi.
- 来得还真是快 - 喔 我们就在附近
- That was fast. - Yeah, we were very close.
我是伊森 这是彼得
I'm Ethan, this is Peter.
- 你是个警察吗? - 怎么了 你是无照的药剂师吗?
- Are you a cop? - Why? Are you not a licensed pharmacist?
你模样看起来像是政府部门的
Okay, you just look really official.
如果你是警察 那我问你的时候 你有义务说是
And you know if I ask you if you're a cop and you are a cop, you have to say yes.
没这回事 警察没这义务 不过我也不是警察
That's a myth. That's actually incorrect. But I'm not.
- 他是个建筑师 - 我是个建筑师
- No, he's an architect. - I'm an architect. So....
- 没这回事吧? - 对啊
- Wait, it's a myth? - Yeah.
天啊!我还一直不知道呢
Shit! I did not know that this whole fucking time.
- 那就好 - 你的模样还挺吓人的
- That's good news. - You're fucking scary, is what you are.
- 进来吧 伊森 药局在厨房里 - 谢谢
- Come in. The pharmacy's in the kitchen. - Thank you.
喂 彼得 你能帮我照看一下孩子 我和他要...你知道的
Hey, Peter, can you watch my kids just for five minutes, while we han... You know.
- 快点吧 - 感谢
- Real quick. - Thanks.
你是谁?
Who are you?
我是彼得
I'm Peter.
我是亚历克斯 这是帕特里克
I'm Alex. This is Patrick.
好极了 亚历克斯 你妈给你取个男孩的名字
Great. Alex. Mommy gave you a boy's name.
那句话什么意思?
What's that supposed to mean?
亚历克斯也是男孩的名字
Alex is also a name for a boy.
因此你被你妈害惨了
So your mom kind of screwed you.
抱歉 我手滑了
Sorry, my hand slipped.
这是刚进的货混合 野寡妇 AK- 47的一种阿富汗大麻
That one I just got in. It's an Afghan blend of Wild Widow and AK- 47.
你知道我不喜欢混合物
You know, I'm not crazy about blends.
我发现味道根本不纯正
I find that the high is a bit shapeless.
喜欢纯的 嗯 那好
A purist. Well, that's cool.
那你应该会喜欢 北极光
You'd probably love Northern Lights.
我的意思是 这形状好 气味也非常棒 如梦似幻
I mean, this has got great body. It smokes like a fucking dream.
噢 他是巴里 在我这里租了一个房间
Oh, that's just Barry. He's renting a room from me.
嗨你好 巴里 我是伊森
Hey, Barry. How you doing? I'm Ethan.
你有录下 法官马西斯吗?
Listen, did you remember to TiVo Judge Mathis?
有啊 录下了 在目录上有
Yeah. It's on there, if you just look at the menu.
你的头发烫得好 烫得真好
Nice perm, man. Well done. Well done on that perm.
噢 谢谢 这不是烫的 天生如此
Oh, thanks, bro. It's not a perm, it's natural.
现在谁还烫头发啊
Nobody gets perms anymore.
等等 别告诉我 你头发是烫的?
Wait, wait. Don't tell me. Is that a perm?
是的 是烫发
Yeah. It's a perm. Yeah.
噢 我的天啊 连头发都是假的
Oh, my God. You didn't have your real hair.
- 现在还有理发师烫发吗? - 谁说不是呢....
- Where do you even get those anymore? - I know! It's like....
我开玩笑的 这不是烫发
I was just kidding about... This isn't a perm.
- 请再说一遍? - 这不是烫的 我开玩笑的
- Excuse me? - This isn't a perm. I was joking.
- 噢 天啊 我还真以为是.. - 哈 哈!
- Oh, my God. Thank God. Because I was... - Ha, ha!
我们都被你骗了 老兄
You got us. You got us both, man.
是啊 只有白痴才会去烫头发
You know, only, like, fucking jerk- offs get perms.
- 那还好 非常好 - 你装的真像
- That was good. Very good. - That was hilarious.
- 你从哪儿来? - 洛杉矶
- Where are you from? - Los Angeles.
- 你正要回洛杉矶? - 嗯
- Is that where you're going? Mm- hm.
你能带着我们一起走吗?
Can you take us with you?
不行 不过有个专门的 儿童权利保护机构
No, but there's an organization called Child Protective Services.
- 这是什么? - 是条领带 你从未看过领带吗?
- What's this? - It's a tie. You've never seen a tie before?
你为什么系领带?
Why do you wear it?
不为什么
Because I wear it.
- 看起来傻呼呼地 - 嗯 不是的
- It looks stupid. - Well, it's not.
你的手别碰我
Just take your hands off of me.
请不要这么做了
Please stop doing that.
放手 请不要这么做了
Stop. Please stop doing that now.
我没碰你 是它碰你
- Will you please...? - It's Reggie.
真的吗? 那就让它歇一会吧
Is that right? Well, maybe Reggie needs to take a nap.
喂 放手 我是认真的
Hey, quit it. I'm not kidding.
你怎么了? 小家伙
You okay, bubba?
- 怎么了 - 没什么
- What? - Nothing.
"没什么" 就对了
"Nothing" is right.
现在 你来告诉我 你说..
And now, you come to me and you say:
"唐 科里奥 为我主持公道吧 "
"Don Corleone, give me justice."
但是你甚至没有叫我 教父
But you don't even have the decency to call me the Godfather.
并且你到我家里...
And you come to my house...
还是我女儿结婚的这一天...
...on the day that my daughter is to be married...
你让我去杀死某人
...and you ask me to kill someone.
还是为了钱
For money.
这可不是公道的
But that is not justice.
真是厉害 第二段听得我热血沸腾
That's amazing. I had chills, like, that second paragraph.
那段台词 那段谋杀 真是精彩 伊森
When the line... The murder. That is so fucking good, Ethan.
谢谢 我还一直在研究用 什么样的手势效果最好
Thank you. I've been working on the hand gestures to get it right.
那是你自己写得吗?
Did you write that yourself?
不! 是黑手党写的
No. The Mafia wrote it.
噢 原来如此.... 无论如何 很高兴见到你
Oh, that was so... It was nice meeting you, anyway.
老实点 否则我还揍你
Play it cool, or I'll thump you again.
当然 不客气 你准备好了吗?
Sure, sure. You all set?
好了 可以走了
Yeah. Good to go.
这两个孩子都听话吗?
How were they? They behave themselves?
听话 真听话
Pretty much. Pretty much.
- 噢 那就好 - 是的-
Oh, good. Yeah.
我的意思是 他们都是好孩子
I mean, they're great kids.
我走了
We good?
- 再见 祝你好运 - 再见
- See you. Good luck. Bye- bye. - Bye.
祝你演艺事业取得成功
Good luck with your acting stuff.
...正判断性格
...is judging the character.
当一名演员在拍摄之前...
When an actor is preparing a scene...
首先要做的是把剧本 看读很多遍
...first thing is read the scene over many times.
先不要让剧本适合自己 先让自己适应剧本
First, before you do any work on it, let it work on you.
一遍一遍的读看 如果可能的话 看整部剧本
Read the material over and over again. The entire script, if at all possible.
喂 大明星
Hey, Hollywood.
信用卡被拒绝了
Card's been declined.
- 什么? - 你的信用卡 里面没钱了
- What's that? - Your card? It's no good.
- 噢 天呀 - 没关系
- Oh, gosh. - It's okay.
你知道吗 肯定是租这辆车时 钱都花出去了
You know what? I bet I tapped it out when I rented this car.
那就支付现金吧 你身上有多少钱?
Great. We'll pay cash. How much you got?
60块钱
Sixty bucks.
你总共就只有60块钱?
You have 60 bucks entirely?
- 是啊 - 你买大麻花了多少?
- Yes. - How much did you spend on marijuana?
- 在你的药上 - 不晓得 大概在200块钱左右
- On your medicine? - I don't know, around 200 bucks.
- 200块钱? - 对啊
- Two hundred bucks? - Yeah.
一路上加油 吃饭 住宿 一切就靠这 60块钱吗?
Sixty bucks for gas, food, lodging, everything?
当地只有她手上有货 价格肯定要高一点
She's the only dealer in town. She names her price.
你几乎把所有钱都用来买毒品 你当时是怎么想的?
What were you thinking when you spent almost all of our money on drugs?
- 我没想到吃饭 住宿的事 - 那你在那想到什么了?
- I don't think in those terms. - What terms do you think in?
我又不是会计 甚至不是犹太人
I'm not an accountant. I'm not even Jewish.
- 那你总该是个成年人? - 那当然 我都23岁了
- Are you an adult? - Of course I'm an adult. I'm 23 years old.
从没见过你 这么愚蠢的23岁的人
You are the most shot- out 23- year- old I've ever seen.
你是怎么活到这么大的? 怎么没被车碾过去?
How have you made it? How have you not run yourself over?
我被有碾过去
I've done that.
你是怎么活到现在的? 我的真是不明白
How have you survived? That's my question.
- 主要靠运气 - 对喔
- Mostly luck. - Yeah.
我也这么想 你也只有靠运气了
That's what I thought. Just dumb fucking luck.
- 我操 - 干什么啊? 彼得
- Fuck me. - Whoa! For heaven's sakes, Peter.
- 我们完了 伊森 - 为什么会这样说?
- We're screwed, Ethan. - How so?
- 你把钱都用来买大麻了! - 这只是小小的挫折
- You spent all our money on weed! - It's just another speed bump.
你知道吗? 我还是给我老婆打电话 让她给我汇款 就这么办
You know what? I'm gonna call my wife. She's gonna wire me money. That's it.
她不能 你没有身分证
She can't. You don't have an lD.
对 那就汇给你 看见吗? 这才是成年人处里问题的方式
She'll wire it to you. See? That's an adult solving a problem.
- 我们走吧 - 我就说嘛 我运气好
- Let's go. - I told you I was lucky.
你就上车吧
Get in the car.
等一下 我去买本杂志做简报用 好吗?
Hold on one second. I'm gonna go get a brochure for my scrapbook, okay?
- 你的姓怎么拼写? - T- R- E- M- B- L- A- Y
- How do you spell the last name? T- R- E- M- B- L- A- Y.
好了 500美元 伊森·崔布雷
Here we go. Five hundred dollars. Ethan Tremblay.
我只需要再看 身分证明就可以了
I just need to see an ID.
在这儿 给您
There you go.
嗯 上面写的不是 崔布雷
Yeah, this doesn't say Tremblay.
而是 伊森 雀斯
It says Ethan Chase.
噢 天啊 他说的对 他是对的
Oh, jeepers creepers. He's right, he's right.
你是什么意思 "他说的对" ?
What do you mean, "he's right"?
伊森·崔布雷是我的艺名 我是一名演员
Ethan Tremblay is my stage name. I'm an actor.
- 你的艺名 你真实姓名是什么? - 伊森 雀斯
- Your stage name. What is your real name? - Ethan Chase.
- 做艺名不合适 - 你的本名更像是艺名
- It doesn't sound like an actor's name. - Ethan Chase does.
你的艺名算什么狗屁艺名
Ethan Tremblay doesn't make any goddamn sense.
就像是编的一样
It sounds like it was made up.
对啊 是我编的
Yeah, I made it up.
伊森 我知道是你编的 但这是你的艺名
Ethan, I know you made it up. It's your fucking stage name.
你为什么让我老婆把钱 汇到你艺名的名下?
Why did you have my wife wire money to your stage name?
- 我没考虑到 - 没错
- I wasn't thinking. - Right.
我正尽力记住我的新名字
Just trying to commit to the new name.
你俩有话去外面停车场说吧 别在这里谈
Do you guys wanna discuss this, perhaps out in the parking lot?
就等一下 你有其它证明 你名字的东西吗?
One sec. Do you have anything else with your name on it?
- 有啊 当然有 - 很好
- Yes. Of course. - Yes, yes. Good.
我怎么没想到呢?
What was I thinking?
- 他有两个名字 - 那挺好的
- He has two names. - That's fantastic.
就等一下下
But one sec.
- 这是干什么的? - 这是身分证明
- What the fuck is this? - It's an ID.
这是张照片证明
It's a photo lD.
- 不 这个也不能接受 - 为什么?
- No, I can't accept this either. - Why?
因为这只是一张你自己的照片 任何人能拍的照片...
Because it's a picture of yourself. Anyone could take a picture...
穿件圆翻领服装 随便写上名字 并不能证明你的身分
...in a beautiful turtleneck, put whatever name they want.
但他不至于费这么大劲 就为了诈骗区区500元
But why go to all that trouble just for 500 bucks?
那可就难说了 但什么样的人没有啊
I don't know why you would, but you could.
那我只能让我怀孕的妻子 开车去银行
So I get to call my pregnant wife and have her drive all the way to Western Union.
重新汇款 把它送到正确的名下...
Start this whole process all over again, send it to the correct name...
是不是这样?
...and we'll be good.
- 正确 - 那好办
- Absolutely. Great.
但只能到明天了 我再 5 分钟后就下班了
We'll have to do that tomorrow. We close in five minutes.
现在才 6︰35 先生!
It's 6:35, sir.
难道你是老板 你是干什么的? 上下班时间你说了算?
What are you, my boss? You make the hours?
我说5分钟后就下班 在饭店订了位 要和朋友 小孩们吃饭
I say when we close. I got reservations at Chili's. I'm meeting my boys.
- 就因为你要赶饭局? - 对
- You have a reservation at Chili's? - Mm- hm.
提前预订好 聪明 星期三晚上饭店人比较多
That's actually smart. I mean, it gets busy on a Wednesday night.
你就这么一直瞪着我看?
Are you gonna stare at me?
难道你就不愿 尽自己的工作职责?
Do your fucking job until your shift is over, hillbilly.
- 尽你的头啊 你就别指望了 - 喔 真的吗?
- Keep dreaming, faggot. No way in hell. - Oh, really?
对不起!! 让我来吧 彼得 先生
Excuse me, Peter. Sir.
我替我的朋友抱歉 我们真的只需要点钱到洛杉矶...
I'm sorry about my friend. We really just need the money to get to Los Angeles...
因为他的第一个孩子 马上就要出生
...so he can be there for the birth of his first child.
说的很动听 你知道我女儿出生时我在哪里吗?
That's such a sweet story. You know where I was when my daughter was born?
- 饭店里? - 伊拉克
- Chili's? - Iraq.
难道就因为女儿要出生 我就能擅离职守吗?
How about I call my sergeant in Fallujah and tell him your story, see what he thinks?
你不是要下班吗?怎么还说个没完?
Aren't you closing? Is it gonna take a long time?
他是胡说八道 伊森 自称是什么...
He's being sarcastic, Ethan, and also letting us know...
久经沙场的战士 ...
...that he's a "battle- hardened" veteran...
其实顶多去伊拉克游览绕一圈 逢人就吹嘘说
...who did some half- assed tour and talks about it all the time.
你放屁
How dare you.
- 你真行 - 你真变态
- Smooth move, that. - You're sick.
你这下惨了 小子
You fucked up. Bigtime.
- 我惨了? - 没错
- I fucked up? - Yeah.
我怎么惨了
I fucked up bigtime?
你吐痰在自己的窗子上
You spit on your own window.
- 我们走吧 - 喂 小子
- Let's get out of here. - Hey, sport?
你说我去伊拉克游览绕了一圈?
What were you saying about my half- assed tour of duty?
- 对不起 我真不知道 - 不知道什么?
- I'm sorry. I had no idea. No idea what?
- 我是残障吗? - 是啊
- I'm handicapable? - Handicapable.
- 你怎么可能知道? - 我不知道 真对不起
- How could you know? - I couldn't know, and I'm sorry.
听我说 这都怪我 说实在的 我只是今天心情不太好
Can I tell you something? Honestly, it's my fault. I'm just having a bad day.
- 今天心情不太好? - 是的
- You had a bad day? - Yeah.
更惨的 还在后面
It's about to get a whole lot worse.
- 好啦 把东西收起来 - 救命!
- Okay, now put that away before you... Help!
噢 这一下很疼吧?
Oh, I know that shit hurt, huh?
- 啊~浑蛋 - 噢 天啊
- Ah. Fucking hick. - Oh, God.
看不出我有两下子吧
The kid's got moves.
让我赶不上饭局 我就让你爬不起来
You wanna fuck up my dinner plans, I'll fuck you up.
这招我称之为" 独轮车 "
I call that little move "the wheelbarrow."
- 彼得 快起来 起来 - 来啊 来啊
- Peter, get up, get up. - Come on. Come on.
- 这就是银行的待客之道 - 先住手
- Courtesy of Western Union, huh? - Hold on one second.
- 噢 你要去哪里? - 去报警
- Oh, where you going, huh? Call the cops.
报什么警啊
Fuck the cops.
火车来了 呜呜!
Here comes the train. Choo- choo!
下班时间到
It's closing time
我要去赶饭局
Time to roll to Chili's
和朋友吃顿饭
And chow down with my fuckin' boys
你还好吧 伙计?
You okay, buddy?
别叫我哥们 哥们不会在我被揍时 在一边袖手旁观
Don't call me that. Buddies have each other's backs when an assault takes place.
彼得 它是残障啊
Peter, that man was handicapped.
你可以叫我彼得 或者海曼先生
You can call me Peter. Or Mr. Highman.
我叫你雀斯先生 除非你的身份证那也是假的
I'll call you Mr. Chase. Unless that was a fake lD too.
真不明白你要艺名要干什么 你又不是真正的演员
Why you have a stage name is beyond me. You're not really an actor.
你什么意思? 什么叫做真正的演员?
What does that mean, "really an actor"? What is a real actor?
真正会表演才是演员
A real actor is someone who can really act.
嗯 那你说吧 让我表演什么
Well, go ahead, give me an action to do. Give me a scene.
- 不 我不想说 - 你应该说
- No. I don't want to. - You should.
好吧 假如我是茱莉亚·罗伯茨
Okay. I'm Julia Roberts.
你查出来患了绝症
You have terminal cancer.
而我们即将结婚
We're engaged.
你会怎样向我公布消息
Break the news to me.
茱莉亚·罗伯茨 ...
Julia Roberts...
正如你所知 我们即将结婚
...as you know, we're engaged.
我患了绝症
I have terminal cancer.
垃圾
Awful.
- 什么? - 抱歉 这就是我的评价
- What? - Sorry, that's my feedback.
- 我觉得挺好 - 不好
- I thought that was really good. - Nope.
我再给你一个机会 假如今天是超级杯总决赛
I'll give you one more shot. It's Super Bowl Sunday.
你是个职业生涯坎坷的教练
You're a coach with a spotty career.
你们落后31分
You're down 31 points.
你在中场休息室 想要激起队员的斗志
Bust into the locker room and fire the guys up.
让大家都拼了 开拍!!
All or nothing. Action.
- 傻了 怎么可能有这种电影 - 每两年都会有这样一部电影
- Stupid. That would never be in a movie. - It's in a movie every two years.
每两年都会有
Every two years.
好 队员们 我们需要到球场去
Okay, guys, we need to get out there.
真的需要拼搏 波勒德 你打的什么球?
Really need to get going. Pollard, what are you doing?
软弱无力 难道你是娘们吗?
You're acting like a girl out there. What are you, a girl or something?
杰克逊 来啊 老兄你要振作起来
Jackson, come on, man, you gotta get yourself together.
- 难道你也是娘们吗?? - 再刺激你一下 你老婆来电话了
- What are you, a girl or something? - Let's up the stakes. Your wife calls.
她想要和你离婚
She wants a divorce.
- 教练的老婆吗? - 你扮演的就是教练
- The coach's wife? - The coach you're playing.
你老婆来电话 她想要离婚
His wife calls. She wants a divorce.
电话来了
Ring- ring.
喂?
Hello?
队员们 先等一下 是我老婆 她想要和我离婚
Hey, fellas, it's gonna be a minute. It's my wife. She wants a divorce.
嗨 老婆
Hey, sweetheart.
说什么?
What's that?
不 不要..
No, don't...
我现在正忙着呢
This is not a good time.
因为我爸已经去世了 你再走了 我可怎么办啊
Because I lost my dad, I don't want you to leave me right now.
我一个人怎么过啊
I don't wanna be left alone.
我非常想念他
I miss him so much.
你不能这么做
You can't do this.
我买了汽水 还有水
I got soda. I got water.
好啊 好极了
Okay. Great.
谢谢
Thank you.
- 这雨还真不是时候 - 是啊
- Crazy rain. - Nuts.
我想今天就不走了 我们在汽车里睡吧
I think we're done for today. We'll sleep in the car.
好
Okay.
我们明天多赶些路 今天只能....
We'll kill it tomorrow. But this is....
谈谈你爸爸吧 他靠什么生活?
So tell me something about your dad. What did he do for a living?
他是一位公路收费员
He was a toll- booth operator.
是嘛?
Really?
他人缘极好 他热爱他的工作
He was a real people person. He loved his job.
他每天回家来 都笑着说 他的窗口汽车排的最长
He'd come home every night and he'd laugh about how long his line was.
因为经过他的窗口 他都喜欢和别人聊上几句
Because he enjoyed talking to everybody that went through the toll booth.
哦
Oh.
你呢 你爸在哪儿?
What about you? Where's your dad?
嗯....
Uh....
不知道
No idea.
最后一次见到他 是什么时候?
When's the last time you saw him?
1977年
1977.
哦
Ooh.
哇
Ouch.
他到我的房间说 "披特 给你一个重要的任务
Yep. Came into my room, said, "Petey, I got an important job for you.
明天早上5点半 把我叫醒 "
I need you to wake me up, 5:30 tomorrow morning."
我特别高兴 他从未要我做过任何事情
And I was ecstatic because he never asked me to do anything.
一直都以为他觉得我不存在
I didn't even know I existed in his eyes. So....
他能交付我做事 于是我特别兴奋
It was just a big deal. I was so excited.
定了闹钟 也睡不着觉 我整夜看着闹钟
I set the alarm clock. I could barely sleep. I just watched it all night.
到了5点半时 我偷偷地进入他的房间...
When it went off at 5:30, I snuck into his room...
小心翼翼叫醒他
...I gingerly wake him up.
他对着我微笑
He smiled at me.
我第一次看见他笑...
First time I ever saw him...
噢 微笑
...uh, smile.
但是他的行李已经收拾好 放在前门旁边了...
But he had his bags packed by the front door...
然后拿起行李 把它们放进汽车后面...
...and he picked them up, put them in the back of his car...
开车走了
...and drove away.
就再也没见过他
Last time I ever saw him.
真好笑
It's so funny.
哦 天呀
Oh, my gosh.
我爸绝不会这样做 他爱我
My dad would never do that. He loved me.
那个声音是什么?
What's that sound?
什么声音?
What sound?
嗯
Mm.
现在没有了
No, it stopped.
- 你听 又来了 - 是我在自慰啦
- Okay, it's back. - That's me. I'm just masturbating.
什么? 为什么?
What? Why?
这样才能睡着
This is how I go to sleep.
噢 不~不! 别这样 哥们
Oh, don't, don't, don't. Come on, dude.
我就在你旁边耶
I'm right here next to you.
彼得 你闭上眼就是了
Just shut your eyes, Peter.
我根本没看 但是有声音
They're closed. The sound.
你就忍着点吧
Just bear with me.
- 靠 你还要多久? - 噫!
- How long is this gonna take? - Ugh!
如果你一直打断我 那时间可就长了..
If you keep interrupting me it's gonna take a little longer...
通常只需要约35分钟
...but it usually just takes about 35 minutes.
只要35分钟?
Is that all?
干! 你的狗也和你一样
Your fucking dog's doing it too.
桑尼! 别弄了!
Sonny! Stop!
桑尼 不行 别弄了
Sonny, no. Stop.
这才听话
Good boy.
来这里 丑家伙 过来
Come here, garbage face. Come here.
不要去想它 没别的办法了
Don't even think about it. Had to be done.
别这么做
Please. Don't.
真受不了他
Intolerable. lntolerable.
狗娘养的
Son of a bitch.
该死的 真是的 不~~
Goddamn it. No.
怎么会这样
Great. This is great.
该死
Fuck.
不可以..
Don't.
好吧
Okay.
我们今天来到主的面前...
We are gathered in the presence of the Lord and all things holy...
为这位先生送行 我不记得他姓什么了....
...to celebrate the passing of one Mr.... I don't remember his fucking name.
雀斯或者是崔布雷
Chase. Or a.k.a. Tremblay.
愿他永远在主的精神荣光之下
May he forever reside and dwell in the sunlight of the spirit.
阿门
Amen.
你知道吗 我想向你解释一下...
You know, I just wanna offer an explanation, sir...
至于为什么把你留在 20 号州际公路旁边
...as to why you wound up on the side of lnterstate 20.
这不是你的错 都怪你儿子
It's not your fault. It's your kid.
实在是受不了和他一起走
He's an incredibly difficult person to travel with.
实际上 我不知道怎样或者为什么...
In fact, I don't know how or why...
你怎么不把他掐死在摇篮里
...you didn't just strangle him in the fucking crib.
嘿 伙计
Hey, buddy.
忘了什么东西吗?
Forget something?
没有 我....
No. I got....
我买了咖啡
I got coffee.
邓肯面包
Dunkin' Donuts.
我还以为你走了
Thought maybe you left me.
我买了早餐能在路上吃 可以节省时间
I picked up breakfast so we can eat on the road, make up time.
- 那你为何把我的东西留在这里? - 因为那是你的东西
- Why'd you leave my stuff out here? - It's your property.
- 这话也对 - 是啊
- That makes sense. - Yep.
想要我开车吗?
Want me to drive?
- 轮到你开车了 - 好的
- It is your shift. - Okay. Very good.
别的东西我来拿吧
I'll grab the other items.
- 好吧 - 好
- Okay. - Okay.
跟我来 桑尼
Come on, Sonny.
桑尼 来啊
Sonny, come on.
我正在想..."彼得不可能 把我留在这里扔下不管
I was thinking, "There's no way that Peter would have left me here.
虽然我们有些不愉快 但绝不至于扔下我"
We've had our bumps in the road, but he's not gonna leave me."
- 噢 那当然 再说又不是我的车 - 说的对
- Oh, please, no. It's not my car. - Right.
过来 上车吧 桑尼
Yeah. Come on. Get in, Sonny.
你知道吗 我的直觉一向很准
You know, my mind works in mysterious ways.
我就猜想"你不想单独旅行一个人走"
And I thought, "God, why would he wanna travel alone, you know?"
你洗的蛮干净的嘛!
You have a nice shower?
- 是啊 非常好 - 好极了
- Yes, excellent. - Great.
你知道公路休息区的淋浴最棒了
You know, rest areas have the nicest showers.
最棒的淋浴
The nicest showers.
这咖啡真烫
This coffee's hot.
- 这是热咖啡 - 呜!
- It's hot coffee. - Whoo!
- 我们过了密西西比河了吗? - 我们还在德克萨斯州
- Have we crossed the Mississippi River? - We're in Texas.
在密西西比州 就过了密西西比河了
The Mississippi River was the river we crossed in Mississippi.
那太遗憾了
That's too bad.
本来可以在那里为我爸送行的
Would have been a great sendoff for my papa.
把他的骨灰洒在古老的河流里 一直漂浮到新奥尔良 你知道吗?
Put his ashes in the old river. Let the ashes float down to New Orleans, you know?
参加那里的狂欢节
Spend Mardi Gras there.
- 我要打个盹 可以吗? - 他最喜欢爵士乐了...
- I'm gonna get some shuteye, okay? - Nothing he loved more than jazz music...
还有乳房
...and women's titties.
- 我昨晚打鼾了吗? - 嗯
- Did I snore last night? - Mm- hm.
抱歉 我睡觉很沉 这是一种病
Sorry. I'm a deep sleeper. It's a condition.
形容人睡觉沉 往往说 " 那家伙地震了都不知道"
You know when they say, "That guy could sleep through an earthquake"?
我真有一次地震了都不知道
I've actually slept through an earthquake.
有一次我在美国银行的面试 过程中睡着了
I also fell asleep during a job interview at Bank of America.
我昨晚没睡着 现在要睡了
I didn't sleep last night. I'm gonna try now.
你应该自慰看看...
You should have masturbated...
因为我在高潮后 睡的就特别香
...because I had a glorious orgasm and I slept like a baby.
...of a gentle coast
And a sun to maybe dissipate
Shadows of the mess you made
喂! 起来!
Hey! Get up!
伊森 醒醒! 该死的!
Ethan, wake up! Goddamn it!
妈的浑蛋
Son of a bitch.
不!
No!
我的胳臂没知觉了
I can't feel my arm.
发生什么事了?
What happened?
我看看租赁协议还在不在...
I'll see if the rental agreement's in the....
唉 算了 我有保险
You know what? I have coverage.
那还好
That's good.
- 离我远一点 - 天啊 你没事吧?
- Stay away from me. - Jeez Louise, are you okay?
你看我像没事的样吗?
Am I okay? Do I look okay?
我胳臂摔断了 还有3根肋骨
I have a broken arm, three cracked ribs.
我的腋下缝了7针 你说呢?
I have seven stitches in my armpit. Does that answer your question?
不 绝不是没事
No, not okay.
- 彼得 我非常抱歉 - 是吗?
- Peter, I am terribly sorry. - Are you?
桑尼都受伤了 我更惨! 而你一点皮毛都没伤到
Sonny's all banged up. I'm a wreck. You don't have a scratch.
医生说因为我睡得沉 肌肉放松
Doctor said I was in such a deep sleep I didn't tense up.
- 我告诉过你 我睡得很沉 - 是啦
- I told you I was a deep sleeper. - Yeah.
但医生说过在开车的时候 不应该睡觉吗?
Did the doctor say it is not advisable to fall asleep while driving?
我只想闭上眼睛 休息几秒
I was just trying to rest my eyes for a few seconds.
不过你下次应该放松肌肉试试 真的
But seriously, next time try not to tense up. Really.
- 等一下 - 那个是谁?
- Wait a second - Who's that?
他是我的真正的朋友 大老远从达拉斯赶来接我
My actual friend. He's come to pick me up. All the way from Dallas.
- 好吧 那我坐前座 - 不可能 只接我
- Oh, good. Shotgun. - Nope. Not us.
不是我们! 我们再也没关系了
Just me. We're done.
认识你 还真是他妈的荣幸!!
And by the way, it's been a fucking pleasure.
趁我现在神智还清醒 让我告诉你...
But just so my conscience is clear, let me let you know...
为什么不带你一起走?
...why you're not coming with us, okay?
这不是因为你害得我 被赶下飞机 还挨了一枪
It's not because you got me kicked off a plane and shot by an air marshal.
也不是因为被一个残障痛打时 你袖手旁观
Not because you stood by as I had my ass handed to me by a handicapped hillbilly.
当然也肯定 不是因为...
I am certainly not leaving you here...
在我一生最重要的一周 你差点让我死于车祸
...because you almost got me killed during the most important week of my life.
我不带你走是因为一个 更基本的原因︰
I am leaving you here for a far more fundamental reason:
我鄙视你的一切
I despise who you are at a cellular level.
好吧 别人也这么说过 我也正努力去改
I've heard that before, and I'm trying to work on it.
- 很好 现在你再听着 - 嗯
- Great. Now hear this: - Yes.
注意听 我警告你不要去好莱坞
Beware. I'm warning you, don't go to Hollywood.
那里的路不是金光大道 路上尽是
The streets are not paved with gold. They are paved with the carcasses...
像你这样自以为能成功的 蠢货的死尸
...of imbeciles like you who think they're gonna make it.
"拜托你 不要去"
"Pray you, avoid it."
明白了吗? 这是莎士比亚的话 听说过他吗?
Did you get that? That was Shakespeare. Heard of him?
是的 我当然听说过 他是著名的海盗
Yes, I've heard of him. He's a famous pirate.
顺便说一下 他叫莎士大胡子
And by the way, it's Shakesbeard.
让我给你一点友好的建议
Let me give you a little bit of friendly advice.
自称大明星的人 从没一个能成为明星
Nobody who calls themselves "Hollywood" has ever made it in Hollywood.
这我倒从未听说过
That I've never heard before.
桑尼 我会非常想念你的 你这丑陋的浑蛋
Sonny, you will be sorely missed, you little bat- faced piece of shit.
- 我这辈子... - 嗯你就习惯吧
- I have never... - Well, get used to it.
还从没见过 像你这样的!
...in all of my 23 years!
- 走吧 我们快离开吧 - 发生什么事了?
- Come on, let's get out of here. - What the fuck?
- 我们走吧 - 你还好吧?
- We're moving out. - You all right?
- 怎么回事? - 非常感谢你来接我
- What's going on? - Thank you so much.
你骂的人是谁啊?
Who's the dude you yelling at?
就是和他走了两天的路 他净惹麻烦
He's nobody. A guy I was traveling with. He's trouble.
他看起来很悲伤
He looks sad as shit.
- 并且你还对他的狗吐痰 - 我吐痰...天啊 我是这么做
- And you just spit on his dog. - I spit on his d... God, I did.
我发火是因为他特别能让人生气 我没事 走吧
I was seeing red because he has a way of getting under your skin. I'm fine. Let's go.
- 把他扔下不管吗? - 带上他没好处
- You wanna leave him here? - Trust me.
- 皮得 咱两认识多长时间了? - 20年了
- Pete, how long have I known you? - Twenty years.
- 20年 ? - 对
- Twenty years. - Yep.
你的情绪失控了 就要当爹的人了 不能再这样了
Your energy's off. You don't wanna mess your karma up. You have a child coming.
因此不管你之间有啥矛盾 你都需要化解它
So whatever you need to do to fix between you and DeBarge, you need to fix it.
相信我吧
Trust me.
处理好
Make it right.
大明星 过来这里
Hollywood, come here.
- 你看见他多么白痴了吗? - 噢 哇~
- You see what I'm working with here? - Oh, wow.
好了 我已经冷静下来一点
Okay, I've calmed down a bit.
- 你准备道歉了吗? - 什么? 你做梦吧!
- You ready to apologize? - What? Fuck you!
- 噢 别这样啦 - 我们快走吧
- Wait. Oh, no. - Let's go.
彼得 彼得 消消气
Pete, Pete, relax.
处理好
Fix it.
首先 很抱歉我对桑尼吐口水
First of all, I'm sorry that I spat on Sonny.
我没有任何理由这么做
I have no recollection of that whatsoever.
现在 如果你要跟我到洛杉矶...
Now, if you're gonna travel with me to Los Angeles...
我就要和你约法三章 第一
...I gotta give you a couple guidelines. Number one:
只要你问我一个问题 我就会对你发脾气
If you ask me a single question, I'm going to flip out on you.
- 所以不要问问题 了解吗? - 有点 可以
- So don't do that. Do you understand? - Somewhat, yes.
第二 如果不在晚上 也不在床上...
Number two: If you fall asleep for any reason...
你因为任何原因睡着了..
...other than the fact that you're in a bed and it's nighttime...
我就挖出你的心肝
...I will disembowel you.
可以吗?
Make sense?
- 差不多 - 好
- Somewhat. - Great.
第三 如果你对蛋奶烘饼过敏 那就不要吃
Three: If you're allergic to waffles, don't eat waffles.
- 那你别带我到蛋奶烘饼店啊 - 闭嘴!
- Then don't take me to a Waffle House. - Shut up!
- 别上火 - 拿上你的东西到后面去
- Relax. - Get your stuff and get in back.
- 抱着桑尼 - 不要
- Hold Sonny. - Nope.
把狗交给我的话 我就把它撕成两半!!
Hand me that dog, I will rip it in half.
你还是改改自己的毛病吧
You better check yourself before you wreck yourself.
都怪他 我们都被列入禁飞名单
And then, his fault, we're both put on a No- Fly list.
- 禁飞名单? 你吗? - 对啦 只不过...
- A No- Fly list? You? - Yeah, and it just...
更糟糕的还在后面 我觉得它就是个变态
Yeah. Just got worse from there. Because he's pathological, I think.
他直接就用手自慰!
He'll just start beating off.
- 什么? - 是的
- What? - Yes.
- 不用润滑油? - 不 不用 就这么干搓
- No lotion? - No, no, he was dry- docking.
那前面是条水沟吗?
Is that a drainage ditch coming up?
是的 它是水沟
Yes, it is.
- 能不能停一下? - 这就来
- Would you mind? - I'm hitting it.
猛烈点!
Real hard.
伊森 你没事吧?
Ethan, you all right?
是啊 我们没事
Yeah, we're good.
下次不要紧张 记得放松你的肌肉
Next time, don't tense up your body. Just stay loose.
- 前面还有一个 - 想要再整他一次吗?
- There's another one up here too. - Want to hit him again?
我们不能开走你爬山虎
We can't take your Range Rover, D.
没关系开去就是了 我更喜欢那辆卡车
Yes, you can. I prefer my pickup anyway.
- 到了洛杉矶就车托运回来 - 不需要 我周五要去洛杉矶
- I'll ship it back as soon as I get there. - No need. I'll be in L.A. on Friday.
是吗? 你去洛杉矶做什么?
You will? What are you doing in L.A.?
我不想错过你孩子的诞生
I'm not gonna miss the birth of your baby.
但是让我问你 她要剖腹产 你不会觉得烦恼吗?
But let me ask you: Doesn't it burn you up that she's getting a C- section?
我的意思是 她身体原本完美无瑕
I mean, that body was so flawless, just banging.
你怎么知道要剖腹产?
How did you know we were getting a C- section?
她对我说的 喝咖啡吗?
She told me. Coffee?
好的
Sure.
怎么回事?
What is going on?
你在说什么?
What are you talking about?
他怎么对你老婆那么了解?
What's with all these stories he has about your wife?
他俩在大学时谈过?
They used to date in college?
都过去20年了
It was like 20 years ago.
得了吧 你看不出来吗?
Yeah, but come on, you don't see it?
这家伙长的帅 又是橄榄球员 有魅力
This guy's good- looking. He's a football player. He's charming.
- 你别瞎说了 - 他的手也那么好看
- You don't know what you're talking about. - He has beautiful hands.
我看肯定有问题
I think there's something going on.
- 他来了 - 这张照片哪儿来的?
- Here you go. - What's this picture from?
- 什么照片? - 你和莎拉的合影
- What's that? - This picture of you and Sarah.
哦 这是2月份时 我们在圣地牙哥拍的
Oh, yeah, that was February. We was in San Diego.
她没告诉你吗?
She didn't tell you?
她说过遇见你 她没说那..
She mentioned that she bumped into you. She didn't say that...
我们在一起叙旧 一起喝酒 玩得愉快
That we were throwing them back. Getting wasted, having a good time.
只是在重温过去一些事 你知道 只不过....
Just sort of reliving some things, you know, just....
- 她是个好女孩 - 她是啊 她自己都不觉得
- Real good girl. Fantastic. - She is. Slipped her mind.
2月 大约就是9个月以前吧
February. lsn't that about nine months ago?
- 别问问题 - 9至10个月吧
- No questions. - Nine, 1 0 months.
9个月
Nine.
那你名字定下来了吗? 她说你对孩子名字很挑剔
Where you at with the names? She said you were being a real hard- ass.
- 她说这件事了? - 对啊 她发了封电子邮件给我
- She said that? - Yeah, she hit me in a e- mail.
- 你和他的妻子交流电子邮件? - 是的
- You and his wife exchange e- mails? - Yeah.
还交流些什么呢?
What else do you exchange?
- 伊森 - 交流体液吗?
- Ethan. - Body fluids?
- 他什么意思? - 我什么都没听见
- What is he talking about? - I don't even listen to him.
发电子邮件你介意吗? 电子邮件!!
This is not bothering you? The e- mails...
交流精液吗?
Each other's ejaculate?
什么!!
What?
就是乳白色的尿
It's when your urine turns white.
好 在约法一章 你不能 ...
Okay, new rule: You can't...
你一个字也不能说
...say a fucking word.
这咖啡尝起来 味道好像猫尿一样
This is horrible. It tastes like cat litter.
我觉得挺美味的
I think it tastes delicious.
我家里没咖啡了 就用了你们的咖啡
You should. I was all out, so I used the coffee you brought.
噢 天啊!!
Oh, boy.
那是他的爸爸 是他爸爸!!
That's his dad, it's his dad.
好吧! 我再买别的咖啡就是了 我道歉 没那么严重吧?
Fine. I'll buy some other coffee. I apologize. What's the big deal?
咖啡就是他的爸爸!!
His dad is the coffee.
他爸的骨灰装在咖啡罐里
He passed away and his remains were in the fucking can.
让他滚 带上他的狗 赶快走!
Get him the fuck out. The beard, the dog, get him out!
- 现在你知道了吧 - 让他滚出去!
- I get it. - Get him out!
你看!才一会儿 你就受不了他了?
I know. It took eight minutes, right?
噢 天啊! 真愚蠢!
Oh, God! So stupid!
骨灰呢? 我爸的骨灰在那里?
Where are the ashes? Where are my dad's ashes?
别急!!
Relax.
- 他也是不小心的 - 它在那里?
- It was an accident. - Where is it?
- 在那里? - 就在我指的方向
- Where? Right where I'm pointing.
在咖啡机那里
There's the coffee machine right there.
那是咖啡罐 咖啡壶
There's the can, there's the coffeemaker.
我们把骨灰弄出来 我来吧 你别急!!
We're gonna retrieve this. I got it, I got it. Slow down, it's okay.
你冷静一下
Can we just calm down?
让我来吧
Let me take it.
喔 天啊
Oh, God.
你冷静点
Will you relax?
噢!
Oh!
别难过
It's okay.
来 我帮你检
Come here, I'll help you pick it up.
好了
There we go.
来吧 放进去
Get it back in there.
很对不起 我们喝了你父亲
I'm sorry we drank your father.
没关系
It's okay.
你真的不要紧?
Are you all right? Are you sure?
是的 没事 这还有许多的骨灰
Yeah, there's plenty of him still in here.
达里尔只煮3杯咖啡 ...
Darryl only made three cups of coffee...
我估计我爸还剩下8杯
...and I think there's about eight cups of my dad left in here.
很好
Great.
至少他味道尝起来挺好得
At least he tasted good.
还不错
Not bad.
是啊 ! 很浓烈
Yeah, strong.
他口味醇厚
He was full- flavored.
醇香
Robust blend.
他真的很喜爱咖啡
He really enjoyed coffee.
结果最后却被人当咖啡喝了
And in the end, he was enjoyed as coffee.
真是生命的循环
Kind of circle of life.
狮子王的主题曲
Lion King. All that.
我告诉你 你问问题的禁令解除了
I'll tell you what, the moratorium on asking questions is officially lifted.
你随便问吧
Fire away.
好
Okay.
- 你胳臂怎么样了 - 还好
- How's your arm? - Not bad.
你觉得达里尔 与你老婆睡觉了吗?
Do you think Darryl slept with your wife?
- 不会 - 可我觉得有
- No. - I do.
要不然他为什么 将豪华汽车借给你 ?
I mean, why would he lend you this very fancy car...
并且还给你路费? 这是....
...and give you all that walking- around money? It's....
因为他是我朋友
Because he's my friend.
那就是这个原因
That's why.
你去过圣地牙哥动物园吗?
Have you ever been to the San Diego Zoo?
我想问你个问题
I have a question for you.
你这三个问题有什么关联?
How did those three questions come into your head?
我想了想 可能是达里尔 让你老婆怀孕了
I was thinking about your wife and Darryl, Darryl getting your wife pregnant.
生下的孩子就会像斑马一样 黑一道 白一道
What their baby would look like, maybe like a zebra baby.
然后我想 我还从未见过斑马
Then I thought, "Well, I've never seen a zebra."
于是觉得到了加州后 或许应该...
And I thought, "Well, I should maybe go to the San Diego Zoo...
- 去圣地牙哥动物园看看 - 我没去过那动物园
- ...when we get to California..." - Nope, I've never been to the zoo.
问下一个问题吧
Next question, please.
嗨 老婆
Hey, hon.
爱慕 忠贞于你的老公 再德克萨斯州给你打电话
It's your ever- faithful and adoring husband calling from West Texas.
只是问候你一下
Just checking in.
很奇怪你没接电话 你正在与达里尔通话吗?
Weird, it went to voicemail. Are you on the other line with Darryl?
我实际上刚和他谈过...
I actually talked to him...
他说你们在圣地牙哥 度过了愉快的周末
...and he told me about the lovely weekend you guys spent in San Diego.
这和你说的不太一样
Didn't jibe with the way you recounted it...
你俩多发发电子邮件 打打电话...
...so maybe with all your e- mails and phone calls...
争取口供一至
...you can get your story straight.
如果有什么需要我知道的...
If there's something you need to tell me before we go down this road...
请告诉我一声 我会很感谢的
...if I'm gonna have a surprise in the delivery room...
免得孩子生下来之后 我再大吃一惊
...I would just appreciate it that you erase any and all...
给我回电话..
Call me.
- 有没有这回事? - 关于什么事?
- Was I right or was I wrong? - About what?
达里尔和你老婆的事 以及孩子父亲的身份
The Darryl thing, your wife, and the mystery about the baby.
她睡了 我给她留言了
She's sleeping. I left a message.
另外你随便的说起这个话题 让我很不爽
And the casual manner with which you bring up this topic, it makes me edgy.
因此希望你不要再这样了 我会感激你的
So if you wouldn't mind not doing that anymore I'd really appreciate it.
- 我买了些零食 - 我看见了
- I got some snacks. - Yes, I see.
遗憾的是 我需要你来开车 我吃了止痛药
Unfortunately, I need you to drive. I'm on Vicodin.
会嗜睡 所以我不能开车
I'm not supposed to operate heavy machinery.
我告诉你
I will tell you this:
如果你眼皮打架 甚至看起来像打盹 更别说睡着了...
If you blink, if you even look like you might be dozing, let alone fall asleep...
我就要用你的围巾 勒死你
...I'm gonna put hands on you. I'm gonna choke you out with your own scarf.
用围巾缠绕你的脖子周遭 直到你咽气 我肯定做得到
Wrap that thing around your neck and choke you the fuck out. Promise.
好像有点激烈
Seems a bit drastic.
摘掉你的墨镜
Take off your glasses.
刚买的 怎样也要展示一下嘛
I bought them, I wanted to showcase them.
现在是夜晚 你还要开车
It's night. You're driving.
一点小车祸而已嘛 瞧你紧张的
You act like you've never been in a fender- bender.
- 摘掉它 - 好啦
- Remove them. - Okay.
- 震动可乐? 把它喝了 - 没问题
- Jolt Cola? Drink it. - Yeah.
- 别对我比手画脚 - 你喝了就是
- You're not the boss of me, you know. - I know. Just drink it.
拜托
Please.
小金刚
Attaboy.
顺便说一下 我睡着那件事...
By the way, when I fell asleep...
也只有那么一次
...that was a one- time occurrence.
- 我是个成人 不用你操心 - 还有件事 你上过厕所了吗?
- I know what I'm doing. I'm a grown man. - Did you remember to use the restroom?
噢
Oh.
嘿 你 独自一人
Hey you, out there on your own
一丝不挂的坐电话旁
Sitting naked by the phone
你会触摸我吗?
Would you touch me?
嘿 你 耳朵贴在墙上
Hey you, with your ear against the wall
等待别人的呼唤 你会触摸我吗?
Waiting for someone to call out Would you touch me?
嘿 你 可以帮助我搬起石头吗?
Hey you Would you help me to carry the stone?
打开心扉 我快回家了
Open your heart, I'm coming home
这是好东西
This is some stuff.
这扇窗子打不开
This window is not working.
不 是我锁上 在里里熏一熏
No, I locked them so we could get a good clambake going on in here.
这样让桑尼也吸一点
That way, Sonny could get stoned.
我吸毒了吗?
Am I stoned?
你感觉到了吗?
Do you feel stoned?
可这只是幻想
But it was only fantasy
不管他怎样努力 都无法挣脱
No matter how he tried He could not break free
虫子在腐蚀他的脑
And the worms ate into his brain
嘿 你 不要告诉我一线希望都没有
Hey you Don't tell me there's no hope at all
在一起 我们站起来
Together we stand
分开了 我们倒下
Divided we fall
然后呢? 怎怎解决的?
Then what? How did it resolve?
嗯 后来发现乳酪研磨器 是在褥垫下面
Well, it turns out the cheese grater was underneath the mattress.
哈 哈!那如此复杂 又有感情
Ha, ha! That is so sophisticated. And has heart.
电视剧有感情
The show has heart.
你怎么对此知道那么多?
How do you know so much about this?
我管理这个电视剧的一个粉丝网站 非官方的 我管理这网站约6年了
I run a fan site for the show. Not official, but I've run a fan site for about six years.
开始是在一间网吧建立
I started it at an internet caf?
过去经常泡网吧
Used to go in there and wash my feet.
叫什么网站?
What was the site called?
下雨了 好汉两个半.com
It'sRainingTwoAndAHalfMen.com.
哇呜
Wow.
厉害 我能收回以前对你 所有不好的评价吗?
That is sublime. Can I retract every derogatory statement I've made about you?
谢谢你 彼得 非常棒
Thank you, Peter. That's very sweet.
- 给我一块 - 当然
- Hand me a Bugle. - Sure.
谢谢
Thank you.
- 给狗也吃1块 - 好啊
- Will you feed one to the hound? - Very well.
我们在高速公路上吗?
Are we on the highway still?
放心 彼得 我自有分寸
Relax, Peter, I've got it covered.
你肯定吗?
Are you certain?
你是因为吸了大麻 才疑神疑鬼
You're getting paranoid. That pot got to you.
好 你看见那个标牌了吗?
Okay. All right, you see the flag?
看起来像边界牌 上面写着"墨西哥"
It looks like a border crossing, it says "Mexico"...
- 噢 天啊 - 又怎么了?
- Oh, Lord. Gosh. - What?
我还以为是加油站 我们汽油不多了
I thought that said Texaco. We're low on gas.
- 好吧 我们没事 - 没事?
- Okay, we're fine. Yep.
我们没事 没事
We're good. We're good.
你打算怎么说?
What are you gonna tell them?
我就说 "你看 我们弄错了"
All I'm gonna do is say, "Look, we made a mistake."
- 然后要求调头转回美国 - 没错
- And we're gonna ask to turn around. - Perfect.
好 你坐直了 什么话都不要说
Okay, I need you to be quiet. Sit straight. Don't say anything.
如果他们问我问题 我不说话岂不更可疑!
Won't that be suspicious if they ask me a question?
- 都让我处理吧 - 就交给你处理
- Let me handle everything. - You handle it.
- 我们去了 - 喔 他正看着我
Here we go. - Uh- oh. He's looking right at me.
彼得 你什么话也别说 好吗?
Peter, please be quiet, okay?
对不起
I'm sorry.
你好 很不幸地 我们走错路了
Hello. The weirdest thing happened. We just kind of got shifted...
你们是美国公民吗?
Are you guys American citizens?
是 是的 我们都是
Yes. Yes, we are.
- 你们两个吗? - 是的 绝对
- The both of you? - Yes, absolutely.
能看看你的护照吗?
Can I see your passports?
我们没有护照
We don't have passports.
问题是我们没想到会来这里
The thing is, we didn't mean to end up here.
肯定是走错路了 因此.... 然后就到这里来了
Somehow, I must have taken the wrong exit, and we're here, so....
能让我们调头转回去吗?
If we could just maybe turn around and go back?
你想要调头转回去?
You wanna turn around?
是啊 我们走错路 我们本来是要去....
Yeah, it was a mistake. We're trying to get back...
你的朋友怎么了?
What's wrong with your friend?
彼得 别这么做
Peter, don't do that.
你的眼睛怎么发亮? 开派对了?
Why are your eyes so glassy? You been partying?
不是 我有青光眼
No, I have glaucoma.
你的朋友 他也有青光眼吗?
What about your friend, does he have glaucoma too?
回答他 你有青光眼吗? 不 他没有青光眼
Answer the man. Do you have glaucoma? No, he doesn't have glaucoma.
那狗也有青光眼吗?
What about the dog, does he have glaucoma?
因为它的眼睛也亮的很
Because his eyes are glassy as fuck.
车子熄火 把钥匙给我
Shut off the car. Give me the keys, please.
就在这里等着
Wait right here.
- 被我搞砸了? - 不 没事
- Did I blow it? - No, we're fine.
你真圆滑
You are smooth.
- 哇 - 把桑尼交给我
- Wow. - Hand me Sonny, please.
天啊 我刚才吓的要命 心都跳到喉咙上了
God, my heart was in my throat. I was flipping out.
把我父亲的骨灰给我 在地板上
Could you hand me my father's ashes? They're on the floorboard.
哇 你要做什么?
Wow. What's...? What are you doing?
我们走错了路 不小心地到了这里
We took the wrong exit, we wound up here by mistake.
不管你问我多少次 我还是这个回答
No matter how many times you ask, that's my answer.
你就像是 杰森 柏恩一样 老兄
You sound like Jason Bourne, man.
你不知道你要去哪儿 没有身分证
You don't know where you're going. No ID.
我想联系美国领事馆
I wanna speak to the American consulate.
我是美国人 我有权利
I'm American, I have rights.
- 噢 当然 没错 - 谢谢你
- Oh, yeah, sure. - Thank you.
喂 拉蒙 他要找领事馆谈谈
Hey, Ramon. He wants to talk to his consulate.
你好 先生 欢迎到美国领事馆来
Hello, sir. Welcome to the American consulate.
- 我能帮你吗 - 这根本是胡闹
- How can I help you? - That's unacceptable.
你们笑什么? 这是严肃的事 我有权利
What are you laughing about? This is a serious matter. I have rights.
你们美国人偷渡进我们的国家
You americanos sneak into our country.
带来了毒品 派对 还和我们的妇女睡觉
You bring drugs, you party. You sleep with our women.
我从未听说过 美国人偷渡到墨西哥
I've never heard of an American sneaking into Mexico.
这是个独立的意外事件 通常是偷渡到美国
This would be an isolated incident. It's usually the reverse.
我受够了 你吊儿郎当的态度
I'm getting tired of your cavalier attitude.
嗯 对不起 很对不起
Well, I apologize. I'm sorry.
你试图把毒品运送过国际边境 ...
You attempted to transport drugs across an international border...
老兄啊
...dude.
这可不是小事啊
This is serious shit.
这笨蛋以为这点大麻 就会让他坐牢
不过这大麻还真不赖
那当然啰 治疗青光眼的大麻嘛
好 爸爸
Okay, Daddy.
来
There.
天啊!
Shit!
妈的 浑蛋!
Son of a bitch!
停车!
Stop!
救命啊!
Help!
噢 糟糕
Oh, shoot.
- 停到路边! - 天啊 怎么回事?
- Pull over! - What the fuck?
把车停下来!
Pull the car over!
坐稳了 桑尼 会有些颠颇
Hold on, Sonny, it's about to get rough.
哇 天啊
Oh, God.
伊森?
Ethan?
大明星!
Hollywood!
噢 惨了
Oh, crud.
彼得 彼得 你怎么样?
Peter? Peter, are you okay?
我们刚刚违反了多少条法律?
How many laws did we just break?
我不知道 有60条吧?
I don't know, 60?
我当时不知道怎么回事
I had no idea where I was going.
然后我看见你 还有... 什么时候我们一起去...
Then I see you. Remember, when we jackknifed together?
- 但是样子不像你 - 我们对视过一眼
- But you didn't look like you. - We locked eyes.
- 靠 你的样子好疯狂! - 是啊 我是在隐身模式
- God, you looked crazy! - Yeah. Well, I'm in stealth mode.
- 所以才用围巾包着我的头 - 你当时就像个突击队
- That's why I got the scarf on my head. - You were like a commando.
- 你简直就是突击队员 - 谢谢夸奖
- You were a Comanche warrior. - Thanks.
- 是史上最牛的突击队员 - 谢谢
- It was the greatest ever. - Thank you.
不要动 准备好吗?
Don't move. Ready?
干什么? 喔
What? Oh.
这是你的新半身像 哈哈哈!
That's your new headshot. Ha- ha- ha!
- 是啊 - 瞧 这张多好看啊
- Yeah. - How could it not be?
天啊 真是疼死了
God, the pain is extraordinary.
- 能把这张照片发送给我吗? - 好呀
- Will you e- mail that to me, please? - Yeah.
好啦 别吃太多了 彼得
Okay. All right. Just not too much, Peter.
营救 一次勇敢的营救
Rescue. A daring rescue.
- 你回来救我 - 那是当然
- You came back for me. - Of course I did.
你真勇敢
You're so brave.
我保证过的 我说过要把你安全送回家
I made you a promise. I told you I was gonna get you home.
把你安全送回家 对吧?
I'm getting you home safe, okay?
- 我要吻你 - 什么?
- I'm gonna kiss you. - What?
- 我要和你亲热一下 - 不要 !!!
- I'm gonna give you a smooch. - No.
- 来吧 !! 宝贝 - 免谈 !
- Come on, baby. - No way!
- 给我亲热一下 - 别闹了彼得 停止!我在开车呢!
- Give me a little smooch. - Stop, Peter! I'm driving! Oh!
变态!
Sick!
亲到了
You got it.
- 你怎么神经兮兮的 - 你对我有大恩
- Everything's up and down with you. - I owe you bigtime.
要不是你 我绝对见不到 孩子的出生
No way I'd see my kid if you hadn't done that.
绝对没办法
There's no way.
我爱你 哥们
I love you, dude.
我也爱你 彼得
I love you too, Peter.
噢 亲爱的
Oh, dear.
老婆 我真的很抱歉
Sweetheart, I am so sorry.
你知道我这人总爱妒忌 又爱吃醋
You know how I get. I've always been jealous. It's....
我不是说过遇见他了
You knew about that. I told you I ran into him there.
我知道 你没做任何错事 都是我不好
I know, and I know it has nothing to do with you. It's just my shit. It's my shit.
听我的话 好吗? 不要说任何事 就听我的
Just listen to me, okay? Don't say anything. Just listen to me.
我永远不会背叛你 彼得 你是知道的
I would never betray you, Peter, you know that.
我们是一家人
We're a family now.
别的都不重要 你明白吗?
Nothing else matters. Do you understand?
- 你说的很对 - 你安全回家就行了
- You're so right. - Can you just get home safely, please?
- 我爱你 宝贝 - 我也爱你
- I love you, baby. - I love you too.
醒醒 伊森
Wake up. Ethan.
你看看
Check it out.
我跟你说 这不是我编的
I'm telling you, I wouldn't make it up.
你能肯定? 我听说它是人造峡谷
You sure? I could've sworn I read it was man- made.
不是的 非常古老 是历史形成的
Nope. Not correct. Very old. Formed over time.
大峡谷 这是事实
Grand Canyon. Known fact.
彼得 我记忆力很好 我记得...
Peter, I have a photogenic memory. I have recall for...
伊森 我可以保证大峡谷的历史 很古老了 这可不是胡佛大坝
Ethan, I promise you. It's old. It's the Grand Canyon, it's not the Hoover Dam.
嗯 我知道这不是胡佛大坝 那是朝圣者建造的
Well, I know it's not the Hoover Dam, that was built by the Pilgrims.
也不对!
Also incorrect.
不过它很壮丽宏伟
It's magnificent though.
- 你知道不必停下来 - 没关系 这里正好
- You didn't have to stop, you know. - That's okay. It's the perfect place.
我们上路吧 我任何时候都能来
Let's hit the road. I can do that any time.
时间多的是 明早再到洛杉矶也不迟
We've got time. We don't have to be in L.A. till morning.
你不必着急 放松
What are you doing? Relax.
还是按我们原来的计画吧
We should just stick with the plan, you know?
但这不是你计画的一部分吗?
But I thought this was part of the plan.
还是有别的原因?
What am I missing, Ethan?
你现在怎么了?
What's really going on?
当我说大峡谷不顺路时 你说︰
When I said the Grand Canyon wasn't on the way, you said:
"太遗憾了 要是能去就太棒了"
"Too bad, it would've been perfect."
当我们过了密西西比河后 你又说︰
When we passed the Mississippi River you said:
"太遗憾了 我爸喜爱爵士乐和乳房"
"Too bad, Dad loved titties and jazz."
我只不过是...我们还有事做做 而且我不想要耽搁
I just... You know, we got stuff to do and I don't wanna step on it.
我知道你不愿和父亲告别
I know it's hard to say goodbye.
我虽然不认识你爸爸 但是根据你所说的 他是位好父亲
And I didn't know your dad, but from what you've told me he was a great father.
他是个好人
He was a cool guy.
我只是想说
I'm just saying.
我只是建议
I'm just suggesting.
如果不能把他喝到肚子里...
If you got it in you...
应当给他一个体面的归宿
...he deserves a grand gesture.
好吧
Okay.
来吧 桑尼
Come on, Sonny.
来 宝贝 来这里 对啦
Come here, sweetheart. Yeah.
爸爸 你我情同父子
Dad, you were like a father to me.
另外...
And...
没有你我真不知道自己 能不能成功
...I don't know how I'm gonna make it without you.
不过我知道你将会在天堂照看我
But I know that you'll look after me from up there.
我不会让你失望 爸爸
I'm gonna make you proud, Dad.
好了
Okay.
我保证
I promise.
我爱你
I love you.
替我问候妈妈
Say hi to Mom.
再见了 爸爸
Bye, Daddy.
他是个好人 如同我一样 你肯定会喜欢他的
He was a great guy. You would've loved him. He was just like me.
喂....
Hey....
有件事我对不起你 一直想告诉你
There's something I've been wanting to tell you I feel pretty awful about.
这些话不吐不快 我....
I kind of want to get it off my chest. I....
在公路休息站的时候 我确实抛弃了你
I ditched you at the rest stop in Louisiana.
- 什么? - 本来不想回头的
- What? - I had no intention of coming back.
我错了
So wrong.
你为何这么做?
Why would you do that?
因为我是个混蛋 我正在改
Because I'm a pig. I'm an asshole. I'm working on it.
嗯 但你知道嘛 你毕竟带着早餐回来
Well, you know what? You came back with doughnuts.
我认为这就能够抵消 你把我抛弃了
I think that says more about you than leaving does.
因此 ...
So...
这事就...
...just...
你真是大肚 感谢
You're something else. Thanks.
那我就轻松多了
That's a load off.
嗯 我也有件事不吐不快
Well, there's something I've been wanting to get off my chest too.
说吧
Shoot.
我其实不是23岁
I'm not really 23 years old.
我知道啊
I know.
没关系
It's okay.
还有其它事情是 ...
The other thing is...
彼得 ...
...Peter...
你的钱包一直在我这里
...I have your wallet and I've had it this whole time.
什么?
What?
你在说什么?
What are you talking about?
彼得...
Peter...
好了 听我解释
...okay, listen.
你为什么这么做?
Why would you do that?
我在飞机上看到你的钱包 不想要一个人走
I saw it on the plane and I didn't wanna be alone.
父亲去世了 我感到无依无靠
I was feeling vulnerable because of my father's death.
不想要一个人走这么远的路 你知道吗?
And I just didn't wanna go across country by myself, you know?
- 东西全部都在 - 是的
- It's all here. - Yeah.
钱 信用卡 一切用的着的 全部都在....
All my money, all my credit cards. Everything....
一点都没少!
Everything I needed.
一直在你那里!
This whole time.
- 你还在生气吗? - 都过去了
- You're okay with it? - It's in the past.
生气有什么用?
What are you gonna do?
- 那好 - 好
- Okay. - Okay.
- 谢谢你 彼得 - 嗯
- Thanks, Peter. - Yep.
那好 那我们就上路吧
Okay. Okay. Let's just hit the road then, right?
- 你抱着桑尼 我来开车 - 我马上抓住他
- You get Sonny, and I'll drive. - I'll grab him in a minute.
- 我杀了你再说! - 哎唷!
- After I fucking kill you! - Ow!
你这个混蛋
You little thief prick.
去死吧 混蛋
Die, thief. You thief.
别激动啊!
Calm down!
彼得 从1数到10 能帮助你消气!
Peter, count to 1 0. It'll help. Aah!
你电话响了!
The phone's ringing!
- 你好 亲爱的 - 彼得 我要生了
- Hello, dear. - Peter, it's happening.
- 什么? - 我的羊水破了
- What? - You won't believe it. My water broke.
- 怎么会? - 你在哪里?
- How? - Where are you?
我在大峡谷 我马上就到那里
I'm at the Grand Canyon. I'll be there in a minute.
什么? 你说你在大峡谷?
What? Did you just say the Grand Canyon?
彼得?
Peter?
妈 他说他在大峡谷
Mom? He's at the Grand Canyon.
喔 我的天啊
Oh, my God.
- 谁的电话? - 我老婆要生了
- Who was it? - My wife has gone into labor.
- 她不是要剖腹产吗? - 快上车
- I thought we were having a C- section. - Get in the car.
你踩到我的名牌皮鞋了 好啦 好啦!
You stepped on my Capezios. Okay, okay, okay!
我们走吧!
Let's go!
天啊 你真是个疯子
Good God, you maniac.
来不及了 真棒 我将要错过我的孩子的诞生
Not gonna make it. That's great. I'm gonna miss the birth of my child.
我们来的及
We are gonna make it.
谁跟你 我们啊? 不要说"我们"
There's no "we." Don't say "we."
- 好啦 看一下 首先... - 能让我先说吗?
- Okay, look... No. Me first. - Please, can I...?
不行 你不能 我说过我会发火的
No. You can't. I told you I saw red.
我说过我会揍你的 这是我毛病
I told you I was gonna put hands on you. I have a problem.
并且很遗憾地 你成了受害者
And I'm sorry you were the recipient of it.
但是我警告过你
But I warned you.
- 对不起 - 好吧
- I'm sorry. - Fine.
但是将来我们 关系变好的时候...
But in the future, when we're hanging out as buddies...
如果我们闹了矛盾 别打我的脸
...if we get into a fight, don't go for my face.
- 好不好! 我靠这张脸吃饭 - 可以
- That's how I make a living. Okay? - Okay.
还没止血
Still bleeding.
看看置物箱 应该有急救药箱
Check the glove, there's probably a first- aid kit or something.
你自己清理一下
Clean yourself up.
还有一只家伙
Check this thing out.
噢 天啊
Oh, shoot.
我不相信这是我干的!!
I can't believe I did that.
抱歉 彼得 非常抱歉!!
Sorry, Peter. I'm so sorry.
没想到里面有子弹 不好意思 快停车吧
I didn't think it was loaded. Pull over.
- 不行 我要一直走 - 不 开到路边吧
- No, I wanna keep going. - No. Pull over.
- 我不想耽搁 - 停到路边
- I don't want to. - Pull over.
这不是真的 不是真的! 到底是为什么啊!?
No, it didn't happen, it didn't happen! Why?!
- 我震惊啊! - 我疼死了!
- I'm in shock! - It burns!
开到路边! 开到路边!
Pull over! Pull over!
别慌! 别慌!不要恐慌!
Don't panic! Don't panic! Don't panic!
- 噢 不要 - 没错
- Oh, no. - Yep.
一枪正好打在这里
It's right there, yep.
- 真的非常抱歉 - 没关系啦
- I'm so sorry. - Don't worry.
我们必须先止血 把你的围巾拿来做止血带
We gotta stop the bleeding. I need your scarf.
- 我要转身吗? - 不 不用 做止血带 止血带
- Turn around? - No. No, a tourniquet. A tourniquet.
你又干什么啊?
What the fuck are you doing?
转身啊! 冷静啦 我来
Turn around! Stay still. I got it.
好了 你来系它 我只有一只手能用
You're fine. Right here. I need you to tie it. I only got one hand.
伤口很深的 必须送你到医院去
It's deep. We gotta get you to a hospital.
本来就是要去医院 没事的
We're going to a hospital. We're gonna be fine.
喔 天啊 !我做了什么啊?
Oh, God! What did I do?
- 别慌张 慢慢来 - 我做了什么啊? 我做了什么啊?
- Stop freaking out. It's okay. - What did I do? What did I do?
让我们像在厕所一样 练习一下 好吗?
Let's do a little acting exercise like we did at the rest stop in the bathroom, okay?
假如你是排长 我是你的士兵...
You're a sergeant, I'm just a grunt in your platoon...
但是你保证 把我送回情人的身边
...but you promised me that you'd get me home to my high- school sweetheart.
好吧
Okay.
开拍!!
Action.
- 彼得 - 嗯
- Peter. - Yeah?
我呕吐在你的伤口上了
I puked on the wound.
我知道 没关系 伙计
I know. It's okay, buddy.
我需要你来开车 我们走吧
I need you to drive, but we gotta go.
好吗?
Okay?
快啊
Come on.
到后座上去 士兵 难道你是娘们还是其他的?
Get in the back seat, private. What are you, a girl or something?
- 好极了 - 就这样吗?
- Excellent. - Like that?
- 对了 快走吧 - 好的
- Yeah, let's roll. - Yeah, okay.
- 想出来了吗? - 想什么出来?
- Figured it out yet? - Figured what out?
你儿子要出生了 取什么名字?
Your son's about to be born. What will you name him?
- 等生下来就知道了 - 桑尼! 这名字怎么样?
- I'll know it when I see him. - How about "Sonny"?
不行 不能让我儿子 和一条自慰的狗同一个名字
No. Not naming my son after a masturbating dog.
不要听他胡说 桑尼 他喜欢你
Don't listen to him, Sonny. He loves you.
桑尼 不要!
Sonny, no!
桑尼 对不起
Sonny. Sorry.
我们回家了!
We're heading home!
终于赶到了
I made it.
- 好了 来吧 - 我赶到了
- Okay, come on. - I made it.
噢 猴子 猴子 忘了猴子!
Oh, the monkey, the monkey, the monkey.
桑尼 稍等一下 马上回来
Sonny, we'll be right back, okay?
我拿到了
Got it.
噢 干!!
Oh, fuck.
谢谢
Thank you.
有一个要当父亲的 还中了枪 应该??
I have an expectant father and a gunshot victim.
我知道要去哪儿 就在这里
I know where we're going. Right here.
然后在左拐
Then we cut left.
- 糟糕了 - 怎么了?
- Shoot. - What?
忘记为桑尼 开扇窗户了
I forgot to crack a window for Sonny.
- 连车门都没了 伊森 - 对啊 那就好
- The door's off the car, Ethan. - Right. Okay, good.
你看 咱们在一块 什么都能考虑到
See? Together we think of everything.
好 我们到了
Okay, here we go.
- 来 给你整理一下 - 应该的
- Let's get you cleaned up. Right? - Great. Yeah.
眼镜给我
Give me these guys.
这样就好看多了
It's all about to go down.
给你一件背心 把血盖上
Give you a vest, cover up the blood.
我说过 我喜欢你的烫发了吗?
Have I told you that I love your perm?
谢谢你 彼得
Thank you, Peter.
看你精神好多了
Look who's come around.
莎拉
Sarah?
来啊 来 到这里来 我们到了
No, come on, come on. This way, this way. Here we go.
- 你好 - 好了
- Ma'am. - Here we go.
把你的手铐放进口袋里 藏起来
Put your handcuffs in your pocket. Hide them.
- 这是给你的猴子 - 真多人
- Here's the Rally Monkey. - Boom.
- 喔~~ - 深呼吸 用力
- Ohh! - Just keep pushing.
莎拉
Sarah?
- 莎拉 - 彼得?
- Sarah? - Peter?
- 你听见了吗? - 快去!
- You hear that? Go!
- 彼得! - 莎拉!
- Peter! - Sarah!
达里尔 怎么会?
Darryl. What the fuck?
- 喂 喂 - 这家伙是谁啊?
- Whoa, whoa. Whoa, hey. - Who the hell is this guy?
你快走吧 老兄 快走吧
You gotta go, man. You gotta go.
- 彼得! - 彼得 在这里
- Peter! - Peter, it's this way.
天啊
What the fuck?
老公! 老公! 你终于来了!
Baby! Baby, you made it!
- 天啊 彼得 你怎么啦? - 老公?
- Jesus, Peter, are you okay? Baby?
没事 我只是有点失血
No, I just lost a little blood.
- 喔~ 噢 我的天啊! - 大家都不要慌
- Ohh! Oh, my God! - Everybody relax.
不要慌 我们要去医院 好吗?
Relax. We need to find a hospital, okay?
- 你是谁? - 我叫伊森 崔布雷
- Who are you? - My name is Ethan Tremblay.
- 是你丈夫的好友 - 很高兴认识你
- I'm your husband's best friend. - It's nice to meet you.
也很高兴认识你 现在先把孩子生下来吧
Nice to meet you too. Let's get that baby out of your vagina.
好的
Okay.
- 深呼吸 - 噢~~
- Breathe. - Ahh!
看这些孩子
Look at the babies.
看看这个孩子
Look at that baby, right?
你看见了吗?
You see it?
- 喂 怎么样? - 你这淘气鬼!
- Hey. What do we got? - You little rascal.
- 看你做的好事 - 只给我看
- Look what you made. - Show me.
哇 他真可爱
Ohh. He's really cute.
真是个小帅哥
That's a handsome boy.
- 实际上是一个女孩 - 嗯 嗯
- It's a girl, actually. - Mm- mm.
- 是啦 - 没错..
- Yep. - No, the...
格林医生说这是常有的事
Dr. Greene says it happens all the time.
你知道超音波也不是100% 准确
You know, ultrasounds aren't always reliable.
对
Right.
- 小罗西 - 罗西?
- Little Rosie. - Rosie?
小罗西 海曼 你觉得这名字很别扭吗?
Little Rosie Highman. Does that sound strange to you?
不会 这名字很好听
No, it's such a pretty name.
莎拉觉得你会同意
Sarah thought you'd be okay with it.
- 你什么时候对莎拉说过话? - 在剪断脐带的时候
- When did you talk to Sarah? - Right after I cut the umbilical cord.
- 你剪断的? - 连接母子的脐带吗?
- You cut it? - The tether of life from mother to child.
我必须剪断
I got to cut that.
- 不会吧 - 没错
- No. - Yes.
- 是你吗? - 我还保留了一点
- You? - I kept some.
留了点把它 放进我的钱包里
I kept a little bit of it and put it in my wallet.
- 能够治疗脚踝扭伤 - 哇~
- It's good for sore ankles and stuff. - Wow.
哇 真扯
Wow. Oh, my God.
噢 天啊 伊森 我作过这样的梦
Oh, my God. Ethan, I dreamt this.
- 说来也怪 我做了个奇怪的梦... - 是吗?
- This is crazy. I had this strange dream... - Yeah?
那是今天
...that was today.
而且还有一头熊
And there was a bear.
什么?
What?
- 熊咬断了脐带 - 嗯
- And the bear chewed the cord. - Mm- hm.
简直就是 完全应验了....
That's spot- on if you think about it. That's like a one in a....
你明白我的意思吗?
You know what I mean?
- 不太明白 什么..? - 算了吧
- I don't get it. What...? - Forget it.
这....这...
It's... It's....
肯定是个好兆头
It's gotta be a good sign.
我就不耽误你们一家人团聚...
I guess I'll maybe leave you with your family...
而且我还要和经纪人见面
...and I got that meeting with that agent.
- 今天正是周五 - 对的
- It's Friday. - Yeah.
是啊 祝你好运
Yeah, good luck.
噢 对了 这个给你
Oh, I wanted to give you this.
上面有我的联络方式
It has all of my information.
- 嗯 - 如果你想找人买汽水
- Mm- hm. - ln case you wanna get a soda.
- 或者是找人照看孩子之类的 - 是
- Or, you know, I could babysit. - Right.
我会留着的
I'll keep it handy.
我们这几天真是疯狂啊
We had a crazy few days.
太疯狂了
That was nuts.
如果以后有时间 再一起长途旅行吧
We should do it again. Go across country again.
好哦
Okay.
- 当然 - 考虑好了明天给我电话
- Sure. - Call me tomorrow about it.
- 如果我不的话 - 明天给我打电话
- If I don't... - Call me tomorrow about it.
我可以用电子邮件给你 请不要介意
I might e- mail you. Please don't take it personally.
没事 电子邮件也可以的
No, no, e- mail's fine.
- 再见 桑尼 - 我和桑尼能开你的卡车吗?
- Bye, Sonny. - Do you mind if Sonny and I take the truck?
请便
Feel free.
- 认识你很荣幸 彼得 - 一起经历过许多事情
- It's been a real pleasure, Peter. - Been a lot of things.
谢谢
Thanks.
喂 伊森
Hey. Ethan.
欢迎到好莱坞来
Welcome to Hollywood.
什么意思? 你还有话想要说吗?
What? You want me to come back and talk to you?
不是 就是非常普通的那个意思
I was just saying in the most general sense.
这个城市欢迎你
The city welcomes you.
明天你记得打电话给我 就是了
Just make sure you call me tomorrow.
我会打电话给你
I'll call you.
我来了
Be right there.
你好吗?
Hello?
噢 嗨 我是斯图 家庭教师 你是杰克吗?
Oh, hey. I'm Stu, the tutor. Are you Jake?
不 我是他父亲
No, I'm his father.
哦
Oh.
我是斯图 家庭教师
I'm Stu, the tutor.
对啦
Right.
你吸大麻了?
Have you been smoking pot?
不 先生 一点也没有
No, sir. Not at all.
应该是我的猫的气味
Perhaps you're smelling my cat.
- 你的猫吗? - 是的 先生 他是只野猫
- Your cat? - Yes, sir. He's an outdoor cat.
你知道嘛 他挺幽默的
You know what, he's really funny.
别夸他 幽默的是电视剧
Don't get crazy. I'm telling you, the show's funny.
得了吧 其实你是喜欢他的
Come on. You love him. You know you love him.
我没被他害死 不等于喜欢他
I survived him. There's a difference.
嗯 查理 这位是杰克的 家庭教师 斯图
Um, uh, Charlie, this is Jake's tutor, Stu.
- 嘿 你好 - 我没抽大麻老兄 是我的猫身上的味
- Hey. - I'm not high, man, it's my cat.
别紧张 斯图 我们也不是警察
Relax, Stu. We're not cops.
噢 真的吗?他长得像警察
Oh, really? He sure looks like the heat.
真准时 我对他说过 看过电视就给他打电话
Like clockwork. I told him we'd call him after we watched it.
他很开心
He's excited.
她不是在说他的名字吧
If she says his name, I'll freak out.
吃龙舌兰面包吗?
Pita bread?
豆沙包吗?
Hummus?
都不吃 谢谢你
Again, no thank you.
你还有大麻吗?
You got any more pot?
想要就多加点钱吧
Not for $9 an hour I don't.
我的意思是说 我没有什么大麻
I mean, I don't know what you're talking about.